<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Luigi Pistilli</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Luigi Pistilli</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volonté as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Great Silence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Great Silence is a 1968 revisionist Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci. An Italian-French co-production, the film stars Jean-Louis Trintignant, Klaus Kinski, Vonetta McGee and Frank Wolff, with Luigi Pistilli, Mario Brega, Marisa Merlini and Carlo D'Angelo in supporting roles.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Zwei glorreiche Halunken]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/zwei-glorreiche-halunken/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Zwei glorreiche Halunken ist ein Spielfilm aus dem Jahr 1966. Er entstand unter der Regie von Sergio Leone und gilt als Klassiker des Italowestern, nach Für eine Handvoll Dollar und Für ein paar Dollar mehr der dritte Teil von Leones „Dollar-Trilogie“, in der jeweils Clint Eastwood eine der Hauptrollen spielt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/zwei-glorreiche-halunken/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr ist ein Italowestern von Sergio Leone aus dem Jahr 1965, der als Nachfolger des Films Für eine Handvoll Dollar entstand. Er ist der zweite Teil der Dollar-Trilogie von Leone. In der Hauptrolle ist wiederum Clint Eastwood zu sehen, der sich in der Rolle eines Kopfgeldjägers mit dem von Lee Van Cleef gespielten Colonel Mortimer zu einem unschlagbaren Team zusammenrauft.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django, der Rächer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/django,-der-rächer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django der Rächer ist ein Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1966, dem der Django-Titel aus kommerziellen Gründen gegeben wurde. Er entstand vor dem Kassenschlager desselben Titels, wurde in Deutschland allerdings nach diesem, am 27. Februar 1967, erstaufgeführt. Videotitel des Filmes war Django 2.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/django,-der-rächer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Leichen pflastern seinen Weg]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/leichen-pflastern-seinen-weg/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Leichen pflastern seinen Weg ist ein Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1968 mit Jean-Louis Trintignant und Klaus Kinski in den Hauptrollen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/leichen-pflastern-seinen-weg/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Von Mann zu Mann]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-mann-zu-mann/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Von Mann zu Mann ist ein Italowestern von Giulio Petroni aus dem Jahr 1967. Die Filmmusik schrieb Ennio Morricone; ein Alternativtitel ist Die Rechnung wird mit Blei bezahlt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-mann-zu-mann/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:44 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>