<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Alberto Dell’Acqua</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Alberto Dell’Acqua</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boot Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Boot Hill is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Terence Hill and Bud Spencer. This film is the last one in a trilogy that started with God Forgives... I Don't! (1967), followed by Ace High (1968).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film written and directed by Enzo Barboni and produced by Italo Zingarelli. The film stars Terence Hill and Bud Spencer as two brothers, Trinity and Bambino, who help defend a Mormon settlement from Mexican bandits and the henchman of the land-grabbing Major Harriman. It was filmed on location in Lazio, Italy, with financial backing from West Film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kill Them All and Come Back Alone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/kill-them-all-and-come-back-alone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Kill Them All and Come Back Alone is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. It stars American actors Chuck Connors and Frank Wolff, and features a film score by Francesco De Masi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/kill-them-all-and-come-back-alone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors is a Technicolor 1966 Italian spaghetti western. It is the directorial debut film of Franco Giraldi, who was Sergio Leone's assistant in A Fistful of Dollars. The film gained a great commercial success and generated an immediate sequel, Up the MacGregors! (1967), again directed by Giraldi, and a later sequel, More Dollars for the MacGregors (1970).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[100 Fäuste und ein Vaterunser]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/100-fäuste-und-ein-vaterunser/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[100 Fäuste und ein Vaterunser is an Italian-German film directed by Mario Siciliano. It was released in 1972.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/100-fäuste-und-ein-vaterunser/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Panhandle 38]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/panhandle-38/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Panhandle 38 is a 1972 Italian comedy-western film. The film represents the debut and the only film directed by Toni Secchi, that had previously been the cinematographer of a number of successful spaghetti westerns. It was also the only leading role for Scott Holden, the son of William Holden and Brenda Marshall, who had a brief film career in early 70s.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/panhandle-38/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die is a 1968 Italian spaghetti western. It is the fourth and last western directed by Franco Giraldi. It was originally intended as being directed by Sergio Corbucci and the cast was to include also Raffaella Carrà and Renzo Palmer. The American version of the film was heavily cut and handled, including a different ending, and it lasts 16 minutes less than the original version.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>