<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Diana Lorys</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Diana Lorys</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[California]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[California is a 1977 Italo-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Michele Lupo. The film was generally well received by critics and obtained a good commercial success at Italian box office.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bad Man's River]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Bad Man's River is a 1971 European comedy Spaghetti western directed by Eugenio Martín and starring Lee Van Cleef, James Mason, Gina Lollobrigida and Simón Andreu. Soundtrack was composed by Tony Duhig, Peter Jonfield, Glyn Havard and Waldo de los Ríos.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Texican]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Texican is a Technicolor 1966 Techniscope film produced and written by John C. Champion and directed by Lesley Selander. It is a paella western remake of their 1948 film Panhandle adapted for the persona of Audie Murphy that featured Broderick Crawford as the heavy. The film was retitled Ringo il Texano in Italy to coincide with the popularity of the Ringo spaghetti western film series.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chino is a 1973 Italian Western film starring Charles Bronson, Jill Ireland, Marcel Bozzuffi, and Vincent Van Patten. The original English language title shown at the beginning of the film was The Valdez Horses, the same title that the novel on which the movie is based. It was an Italian-Spanish-French co-production filmed in Spain, with Italian and French funding.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Heroes of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/heroes-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Heroes of the West is a 1963 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Steno.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/heroes-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gunfighters of Casa Grande]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunfighters-of-casa-grande/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gunfighters of Casa Grande is a 1964 Eurowestern film, co-produced by American and Spanish producers. Based on a story by Borden and Patricia Chase, it was later developed into a screenplay with the assistance of screenwriter Clark Reynolds and directed by Roy Rowland, the last film he made for Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunfighters-of-casa-grande/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django Shoots First]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-shoots-first/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[

Django Shoots First is an Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Alberto De Martino.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-shoots-first/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Mann aus Virginia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-mann-aus-virginia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Mann aus Virginia ist ein Italowestern aus der Endphase des Genres, den Michele Lupo 1977 inszenierte. Der düstere Film kam am 16. September dieses Jahres auch auf deutsche Kinoleinwände.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-mann-aus-virginia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Matalo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/matalo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Matalo ist ein in internationaler Koproduktion entstandener Italowestern, der am 3. Dezember 1971 seine deutsche Erstaufführung erlebte. Trotz Starbesetzung bekam der Film schlechte Kritiken und enttäuschte finanziell. Von vielen Kritikern wird er zu den schlechtesten Filmen des Genres gezählt. Der internationale Titel ist Bad Man's River.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/matalo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Mann aus Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-mann-aus-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Mann aus Texas ist ein mit Spanien koproduzierter US-amerikanischer Western, den Genreveteran Lesley Selander mit Audie Murphy in der Titelrolle inszenierte.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-mann-aus-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>