<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Fabio Testi</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Fabio Testi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Damned Day at Dawn… Django Meets Sartana!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-damned-day-at-dawn-django-meets-sartana!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[One Damned Day at Dawn… Django Meets Sartana! is a 1970 spaghetti western directed by Demofilo Fidani.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-damned-day-at-dawn-django-meets-sartana!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride is a 1971 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Aldo Florio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37 is an Italian-Spanish 1978 Western film directed by Monte Hellman, starring Warren Oates, Jenny Agutter, and Fabio Testi. Noted director Sam Peckinpah has a small, rare acting role. The film was shot in locations in Spain and Italy by cinematographer Giuseppe Rotunno. Pino Donaggio composed the musical score. The film had a very sparse theatrical release in the United States, and did not play in some cities until as late as 1984.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse is a 1975 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Lucio Fulci and starring Fabio Testi, Tomas Milian and Michael J. Pollard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse / Red Coats is a 1975 Italian adventure film co-written and directed by Joe D'Amato. It is part of a brief series of films that tried to market the commercial success of Lucio Fulci's White Fang presenting very similar plots and settings. D'Amato co-wrote the film with writer/actor Luigi Montefiori, who went on to star in a dozen or more D'Amato films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>