<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Genre » Treasure Hunt Film</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Genre » Treasure Hunt Film</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Stranger and the Gunfighter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Là dove non batte il sole, also known as The Stranger and the Gunfighter and El kárate, el Colt y el impostor, is a 1974 kung fu Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Antonio Margheriti and starring Lo Lieh and Lee Van Cleef. It was produced by the Shaw Brothers Studio in collaboration with an Italian company, and filmed on location in Hong Kong and Spain. For English-language release, the film was retitled The Stranger and the Gunfighter and Blood Money.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death is a 1971 Italian/Spanish/German international co-production spaghetti western/ action comedy film directed by Duccio Tessari. The film is mostly a send up of "political" Spaghetti Westerns, like A Professional Gun and Compañeros.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Between God]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/between-god/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Between God, the Devil and a Winchester is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Marino Girolami.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/between-god/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>