<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » John Bartha</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » John Bartha</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[His Name Was King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[His Name Was King is a 1971 Italian Western film directed by Giancarlo Romitelli and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Son of Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/son-of-django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Son of Django is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Osvaldo Civirani.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/son-of-django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Time of Vultures]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/time-of-vultures/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Il tempo degli avvoltoi is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Nando Cicero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/time-of-vultures/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Oro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-oro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ringo and His Golden Pistol is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci and starring Mark Damon.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-oro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Am Sartana, Trade Your Guns for a Coffin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana's Here… Trade Your Pistol for a Coffin is a 1970 spaghetti western that is the third of the Sartana film series with George Hilton taking over the lead role from Gianni Garko. The film was shot in Italy and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man of the East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man of the East is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo Barboni starring Terence Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Return of Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Return of Sabata is a 1971 Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. The third film in The Sabata Trilogy, it features the return of Lee Van Cleef as the title character, which he had played in the first film, Sabata, but was replaced by Yul Brynner in the second film, Adiós, Sabata, due to a scheduling conflict. Return of Sabata was listed in the 1978 book The Fifty Worst Films of All Time.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>