<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Joseph Egger</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Joseph Egger</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Black Eagle of Santa Fe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/black-eagle-of-santa-fe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Black Eagle of Santa Fe or Die Schwarzen Adler von Santa Fe is a 1965 West German and Italian international co-production western film directed by Alberto Cardone and Ernst Hofbauer.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/black-eagle-of-santa-fe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood in his first leading role, alongside Gian Maria Volontè, Marianne Koch, Wolfgang Lukschy, Sieghardt Rupp, José Calvo, Antonio Prieto, and Joseph Egger. The film, an international co-production between Italy, West Germany, and Spain, was filmed on a low budget, and Eastwood was paid $15,000 for his role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>