<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Nello Pazzafini</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Nello Pazzafini</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell, in the original Italian known as Vivo per la tua morte, is a 1968 film directed by Camillo Bazzoni. It is based on the novel Judas Gun by Gordon D. Shirreffs. The film was bodybuilder Steve Reeves' final film prior to his retirement. Reeves, who turned down the lead of A Fistful of Dollars financed and co-wrote the film himself upon seeing the successful box office returns of the Clint Eastwood spaghetti westerns at the time. The film did poorly and Reeves retired from filmmaking that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Colt, also known as The Man from Nowhere, is a Spaghetti Western directed by Michele Lupo and starring Giuliano Gemma, Fernando Sancho and Corinne Marchand.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Am Sartana, Trade Your Guns for a Coffin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana's Here… Trade Your Pistol for a Coffin is a 1970 spaghetti western that is the third of the Sartana film series with George Hilton taking over the lead role from Gianni Garko. The film was shot in Italy and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Find a Place to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/find-a-place-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Find a Place to Die (1968) is a spaghetti western starring Jeffrey Hunter and Pascale Petit. It was co-written and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo with sequences directed by Hugo Fregonese who also produced the film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/find-a-place-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Terrible Day of the Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/terrible-day-of-the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Terrible Day of the Big Gundown is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/terrible-day-of-the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gunman Sent by God]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunman-sent-by-god/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gunman Sent by God is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Anthony Steffen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunman-sent-by-god/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man Called Invincible]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-called-invincible/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man Called Invincible is a 1973 Italian spaghetti western-comedy film directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-called-invincible/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>