<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Mario Brega</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Mario Brega</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West is a 1964 Italian comedy western film directed by Giorgio Simonelli. Its stars Franco Franchi, Ciccio Ingrassia and Fernando Sancho.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe (Italian: Un genio, due compari, un pollo is a 1975 spaghetti western comedy film directed by Damiano Damiani and Sergio Leone, who directed the opening scene.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name is Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[My Name Is Nobody is a 1973 western comedy film starring Terence Hill and Henry Fonda. The film was directed by Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buffalo Bill, Hero of the Far West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/buffalo-bill,-hero-of-the-far-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Buffalo Bill, Hero of the Far West  is a 1964 Italian spaghetti western directed by Mario Costa.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/buffalo-bill,-hero-of-the-far-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Una lunga fila di croci]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/una-lunga-fila-di-croci/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[No Room To Die is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/una-lunga-fila-di-croci/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[La taglia è tua... l'uomo l'ammazzo io]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-taglia-è-tua...-l'uomo-l'ammazzo-io/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Reward's Yours... The Man's Mine is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Edoardo Mulargia.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-taglia-è-tua...-l'uomo-l'ammazzo-io/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Halleluja for Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[La più grande rapina del West is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Maurizio Lucidi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Great Silence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Great Silence is a 1968 revisionist Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci. An Italian-French co-production, the film stars Jean-Louis Trintignant, Klaus Kinski, Vonetta McGee and Frank Wolff, with Luigi Pistilli, Mario Brega, Marisa Merlini and Carlo D'Angelo in supporting roles.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>