<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Osiride Pevarello</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Osiride Pevarello</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Professionisti per un massacro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/professionisti-per-un-massacro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Red Blood, Yellow Gold, is a 1967 Italian-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Nando Cicero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/professionisti-per-un-massacro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[His Name Was King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[His Name Was King is a 1971 Italian Western film directed by Giancarlo Romitelli and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Those Dirty Dogs]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/those-dirty-dogs/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Those Dirty Dogs is a 1973 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Giuseppe Rosati and starring Gianni Garko and Stephen Boyd. The film was made in the later part of the spaghetti western boom. As such it features such latter-day genre elements as self-parody, guffaw humour, near-slapstick fight scenes, machine guns hidden in everyday household items, and bombastic villains.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/those-dirty-dogs/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Return of Shanghai Joe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-shanghai-joe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Return of Shanghai Joe is a 1975 Western film directed by Bitto Albertini and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-shanghai-joe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Vengeance Is My Forgiveness]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/vengeance-is-my-forgiveness/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Vengeance Is My Forgiveness is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Roberto Mauri.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/vengeance-is-my-forgiveness/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugar Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sugar Colt is a 1966 Italian and Spanish spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi, produced by Franco Cittadini and Stenio Fiorentini, written by Sandro Continenza, Augusto Finocchi, Giuseppe Mangione and Fernando Di Leo, composed by Luis Enríquez Bacalov, filmed by Alejandro Ulloa and starred by Jack Betts, Joaquín Parra, Soledad Miranda, Georges Rigaud, Antonio Padilla, Giuliano Raffaelli and Hunt Powers. It is the Giraldi's second film after Seven Guns for the MacGregors. The film represents the cinematographical debut for Jack Betts, here credited as Hunt Powers, and it is also Erno Crisa's last film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django the Bastard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django the Bastard, also known as The Strangers Gundown, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone. This Gothic-themed Spaghetti Western took advantage of the success of Sergio Corbucci's film Django, hence its title. A similar spaghetti western is the 1967 film Django Kill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film written and directed by Enzo Barboni and produced by Italo Zingarelli. The film stars Terence Hill and Bud Spencer as two brothers, Trinity and Bambino, who help defend a Mormon settlement from Mexican bandits and the henchman of the land-grabbing Major Harriman. It was filmed on location in Lazio, Italy, with financial backing from West Film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>