<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Lionel Stander</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Lionel Stander</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse / Red Coats is a 1975 Italian adventure film co-written and directed by Joe D'Amato. It is part of a brief series of films that tried to market the commercial success of Lucio Fulci's White Fang presenting very similar plots and settings. D'Amato co-wrote the film with writer/actor Luigi Montefiori, who went on to star in a dozen or more D'Amato films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Stranger and the Gunfighter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Là dove non batte il sole, also known as The Stranger and the Gunfighter and El kárate, el Colt y el impostor, is a 1974 kung fu Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Antonio Margheriti and starring Lo Lieh and Lee Van Cleef. It was produced by the Shaw Brothers Studio in collaboration with an Italian company, and filmed on location in Hong Kong and Spain. For English-language release, the film was retitled The Stranger and the Gunfighter and Blood Money.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mark of Zorro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mark-of-zorro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mark of Zorro is a 1975 Italian adventure comedy film directed by Franco Lo Cascio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mark-of-zorro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Law]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Beyond the Law is a 1968 Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Stegani and starring Lee Van Cleef as Cudlip, Antonio Sabàto Sr. as Ben Novack and Gordon Mitchell as Burton. It was first distributed in the United States in 1971.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sting-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tedeum is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. The title role was initially offered to Tomas Milian, who eventually refused.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sting-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boot Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Boot Hill is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Terence Hill and Bud Spencer. This film is the last one in a trilogy that started with God Forgives... I Don't! (1967), followed by Ace High (1968).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Die Rotröcke]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-rotröcke/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Die Rotröcke ist ein 1974 gedrehter Abenteuerfilm im Umfeld der Mounties in Kanada, den Aristide Massaccesi im Stile der Italowestern inszenierte. Alternativtitel auf Video ist Die gnadenlose Meute. Die deutschsprachige Erstaufführung erfolgte am 17. Mai 1977 im Fernsehen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-rotröcke/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[In meiner Wut wieg’ ich vier Zentner]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/in-meiner-wut-wieg’-ich-vier-zentner/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[In meiner Wut wieg' ich vier Zentner ist ein Film des italienischen Regisseurs Antonio Margheriti aus dem Jahr 1974. Der nach einer Idee von Barth Jules Sussman entstandene Film stellt einen Genremix aus Eastern, Italo-Western und Komödie dar. Der auch als Kung Fu im Wilden Westen gezeigte Film wurde am 12. Februar 1975 im deutschsprachigen Raum erstaufgeführt. Auf Video hieß er Blood Money.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/in-meiner-wut-wieg’-ich-vier-zentner/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ah sì? E io lo dico a Zzzzorro!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/ah-sì?-e-io-lo-dico-a-zzzzorro!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ah sì? E io lo dico a Zzzzorro! ist eine 1975 entstandene Filmparodie auf Zorrofilme und Italowestern, die im deutschen Sprachraum nicht gezeigt wurde.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/ah-sì?-e-io-lo-dico-a-zzzzorro!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>