<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Luciano Rossi</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Luciano Rossi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hate Is My God]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hate-is-my-god/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Hate Is My God is a 1969 Italian-German Spaghetti Western film directed by Claudio Gora.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hate-is-my-god/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boot Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Boot Hill is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Terence Hill and Bud Spencer. This film is the last one in a trilogy that started with God Forgives... I Don't! (1967), followed by Ace High (1968).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Am Sartana, Trade Your Guns for a Coffin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana's Here… Trade Your Pistol for a Coffin is a 1970 spaghetti western that is the third of the Sartana film series with George Hilton taking over the lead role from Gianni Garko. The film was shot in Italy and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django the Bastard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django the Bastard, also known as The Strangers Gundown, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone. This Gothic-themed Spaghetti Western took advantage of the success of Sergio Corbucci's film Django, hence its title. A similar spaghetti western is the 1967 film Django Kill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film written and directed by Enzo Barboni and produced by Italo Zingarelli. The film stars Terence Hill and Bud Spencer as two brothers, Trinity and Bambino, who help defend a Mormon settlement from Mexican bandits and the henchman of the land-grabbing Major Harriman. It was filmed on location in Lazio, Italy, with financial backing from West Film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Preparati la bara!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django, Prepare a Coffin, alternatively titled Viva Django, is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film stars Terence Hill in the title role, which was previously played by Franco Nero in Sergio Corbucci's original film. Django, Prepare a Coffin is unique among the plethora of films which capitalized on Corbucci's in that it is not only a semi-official, legitimate follow-up, but was also originally intended to star Nero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Sentence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Sentence is a 1968 spaghetti western directed by Mario Lanfranchi and starring Richard Conte.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Los Amigos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/los-amigos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Deaf Smith & Johnny Ears, also known as Los Amigos, is a 1973 Spaghetti Western film starring Anthony Quinn and Franco Nero in 1973. The film is loosely based on the life of Deaf Smith, with direction of Paolo Cavara.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/los-amigos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Man Called Sledge]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-man-called-sledge/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Man Called Sledge is a 1970 Italian spaghetti western film starring James Garner in an extremely offbeat role as a grimly evil thief, and featuring Dennis Weaver, Claude Akins and Wayde Preston. The film was written by Vic Morrow and Frank Kowalski, and directed by Morrow in Techniscope.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-man-called-sledge/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>