<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Manolo Bolognini</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Manolo Bolognini</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[California]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[California is a 1977 Italo-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Michele Lupo. The film was generally well received by critics and obtained a good commercial success at Italian box office.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film is a western adaptation of the Greek myth of Orestes, subject of three famous drama-plays by Aeschylus, Sophocles and Euripides. Ulrich P. Bruckner puts it among the "most interesting and most touching Spaghetti Westerns of the late sixties".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keoma]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Keoma is a 1976 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Franco Nero. It is frequently regarded as one of the better 'twilight' Spaghetti Westerns, being one of the last films of its genre, and is known for its incorporation of newer cinematic techniques of the time and its vocal soundtrack by Guido & Maurizio De Angelis.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rita of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Rita of the West, is a 1967 Italian musicarello-spaghetti western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Preparati la bara!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django, Prepare a Coffin, alternatively titled Viva Django, is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film stars Terence Hill in the title role, which was previously played by Franco Nero in Sergio Corbucci's original film. Django, Prepare a Coffin is unique among the plethora of films which capitalized on Corbucci's in that it is not only a semi-official, legitimate follow-up, but was also originally intended to star Nero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>