<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Fabio Testi</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Fabio Testi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse / Red Coats is a 1975 Italian adventure film co-written and directed by Joe D'Amato. It is part of a brief series of films that tried to market the commercial success of Lucio Fulci's White Fang presenting very similar plots and settings. D'Amato co-wrote the film with writer/actor Luigi Montefiori, who went on to star in a dozen or more D'Amato films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride is a 1971 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Aldo Florio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Damned Day at Dawn… Django Meets Sartana!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-damned-day-at-dawn…-django-meets-sartana!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[One Damned Day at Dawn… Django Meets Sartana! is a 1970 spaghetti western directed by Demofilo Fidani.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-damned-day-at-dawn…-django-meets-sartana!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse is a 1975 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Lucio Fulci and starring Fabio Testi, Tomas Milian and Michael J. Pollard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37 is an Italian-Spanish 1978 Western film directed by Monte Hellman, starring Warren Oates, Jenny Agutter, and Fabio Testi. Noted director Sam Peckinpah has a small, rare acting role. The film was shot in locations in Spain and Italy by cinematographer Giuseppe Rotunno. Pino Donaggio composed the musical score. The film had a very sparse theatrical release in the United States, and did not play in some cities until as late as 1984.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Die Rotröcke]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-rotröcke/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Die Rotröcke ist ein 1974 gedrehter Abenteuerfilm im Umfeld der Mounties in Kanada, den Aristide Massaccesi im Stile der Italowestern inszenierte. Alternativtitel auf Video ist Die gnadenlose Meute. Die deutschsprachige Erstaufführung erfolgte am 17. Mai 1977 im Fernsehen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-rotröcke/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Knie nieder und friß Staub]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/knie-nieder-und-friß-staub/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Knie nieder und friß Staub ist ein Italowestern in spanischer Koproduktion – der Originaltitel des Films ist teilweise spanisch, ein Alternativtitel Il sole sotto la terra – von Regisseur Aldo Florio aus dem Jahr 1971. Der recht harte Film hatte seine deutsche Erstaufführung am 23. Juni 1972.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/knie-nieder-und-friß-staub/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Quel maledetto giorno d’inverno]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/quel-maledetto-giorno-d’inverno/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Quel maledetto giorno d’inverno ist ein im deutschsprachigen Raum nicht gezeigter Italowestern, den Demofilo Fidani preisgünstig 1970 inszenierte.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/quel-maledetto-giorno-d’inverno/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Verdammt zu leben – verdammt zu sterben]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/verdammt-zu-leben-–-verdammt-zu-sterben/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Verdammt zu leben – verdammt zu sterben ist ein Italowestern aus der Spätphase des Genres, den Lucio Fulci 1975 inszenierte. Der wegen einiger brutalen Szenen umstrittene Film wurde im deutschsprachigen Raum am 15. April 1977 in gekürzter Form erstaufgeführt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/verdammt-zu-leben-–-verdammt-zu-sterben/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>