<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Requiescant]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/requiescant/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Requiescant, also known as Kill and Pray, is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed by Carlo Lizzani.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/requiescant/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Mario Gariazzo and starring Ty Hardin, Rossano Brazzi and Craig Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Compañeros]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Compañeros is a 1970 Zapata Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci. The film stars Franco Nero, Tomas Milian, Jack Palance and Fernando Rey. The soundtrack for the film was written by Ennio Morricone, and the orchestra was conducted by Bruno Nicolai.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West is a 1964 Italian comedy western film directed by Giorgio Simonelli. Its stars Franco Franchi, Ciccio Ingrassia and Fernando Sancho.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sartana the Gravedigger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[I am Sartana, Your Angel of Death is a 1969 Italian Western film directed by Giuliano Carnimeo and starring Gianni Garko. The film is presented on some DVD reissues under its German title, Sartana - Töten war sein täglich Brot.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pancho Villa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Pancho Villa is a 1972 American, British and Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Eugenio Martín. The film features Telly Savalas, Clint Walker, Chuck Connors and Anne Francis. Shot in Spain, this "brawling spectacle" has an often-overlooked light-comedy satirical facet, which to this day often confuses the viewers. The storyline was developed during the Vietnam War and reflected certain antiwar sentiments in an American society.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Seven from Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-seven-from-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Seven from Texas is a 1964 Spanish-Italian western film directed by Joaquín Luis Romero Marchent. It was shown as part of a retrospective on Spaghetti Western at the 64th Venice International Film Festival.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-seven-from-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Silver Saddle]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/silver-saddle/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Silver Saddle, is a 1978 Spaghetti Western. It is the third and final western directed by Lucio Fulci and one of the last spaghetti westerns to be produced by a European studio. The film was based on an original story written by screenwriter Adriano Bolzoni and directed by Fulci for the Italian studio Rizzoli Film Productions.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/silver-saddle/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Behind the Mask of Zorro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/behind-the-mask-of-zorro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Behind the Mask of Zorro or E Zorro cabalga otra vez is a 1965 Italian western film directed by Ricardo Blasco.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/behind-the-mask-of-zorro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>