<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Frank Braña</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Frank Braña</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós gringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós gringo is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giorgio Stegani. Its stars Giuliano Gemma and was co produced between Italy, Spain and France. On release in the United States, nearly all of the cast members and production team had their names changed for the English audience. A major success, it was the 4th highest grossing picture of the year in Italy.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Texican]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Texican is a Technicolor 1966 Techniscope film produced and written by John C. Champion and directed by Lesley Selander. It is a paella western remake of their 1948 film Panhandle adapted for the persona of Audie Murphy that featured Broderick Crawford as the heavy. The film was retitled Ringo il Texano in Italy to coincide with the popularity of the Ringo spaghetti western film series.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ace High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ace High is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and written by Giuseppe Colizzi and starring Terence Hill, Bud Spencer and Eli Wallach. The film is the second in a trilogy started with God Forgives... I Don't! and ended with Boot Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Troublemakers]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/troublemakers/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Troublemakers is a 1994 spaghetti western comedy film. It is the last pairing of Terence Hill and Bud Spencer.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/troublemakers/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Coffin for the Sheriff]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-coffin-for-the-sheriff/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Coffin for the Sheriff  is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Mario Caiano and starring Anthony Steffen, Eduardo Fajardo, Fulvia Franco, George Rigaud and Armando Calvo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-coffin-for-the-sheriff/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fasthand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fasthand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fasthand is a 1973 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Frank Bronston and starring Alan Steel, William Berger and Frank Braña.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fasthand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>