<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Ennio Balbo</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Ennio Balbo</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django the Bastard]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django the Bastard, also known as The Strangers Gundown, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone. This Gothic-themed Spaghetti Western took advantage of the success of Sergio Corbucci's film Django, hence its title. A similar spaghetti western is the 1967 film Django Kill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-the-bastard/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gunman Sent by God]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunman-sent-by-god/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gunman Sent by God is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Anthony Steffen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gunman-sent-by-god/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gatling Gun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gatling-gun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gatling Gun is a 1968 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Paolo Bianchini and starring Robert Woods.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gatling-gun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>