<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Luis Bacalov</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Luis Bacalov</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Man Called Noon]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-man-called-noon/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Man Called Noon is a 1973 film directed by Peter Collinson. It stars Richard Crenna and Stephen Boyd. It is based on a 1970 Louis L'Amour novel of the same name.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-man-called-noon/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Bullet for the General]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-bullet-for-the-general/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Bullet for the General is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Damiano Damiani starring Gian Maria Volonté, Lou Castel, Klaus Kinski and Martine Beswick. The film tells the story of El Chuncho, a bandit, and Bill Tate, who is a counter-revolutionary in Mexico. Chuncho soon learns that social revolution is more important than mere money.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-bullet-for-the-general/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[His Name Was King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[His Name Was King is a 1971 Italian Western film directed by Giancarlo Romitelli and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Storm Rider]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/storm-rider/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Grand Duel, also known as Storm Rider and The Big Showdown, is a 1972 Spaghetti Western film directed by Giancarlo Santi, who had previously worked as Sergio Leone's assistant director on The Good, the Bad and the Ugly and Once Upon a Time in the West. The film stars Lee Van Cleef as a sheriff who seeks justice for a man accused of murder.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/storm-rider/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Halleluja for Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[La più grande rapina del West is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Maurizio Lucidi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugar Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sugar Colt is a 1966 Italian and Spanish spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi, produced by Franco Cittadini and Stenio Fiorentini, written by Sandro Continenza, Augusto Finocchi, Giuseppe Mangione and Fernando Di Leo, composed by Luis Enríquez Bacalov, filmed by Alejandro Ulloa and starred by Jack Betts, Joaquín Parra, Soledad Miranda, Georges Rigaud, Antonio Padilla, Giuliano Raffaelli and Hunt Powers. It is the Giraldi's second film after Seven Guns for the MacGregors. The film represents the cinematographical debut for Jack Betts, here credited as Hunt Powers, and it is also Erno Crisa's last film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci, starring Franco Nero as the title character alongside Loredana Nusciak, José Bódalo, Ángel Álvarez and Eduardo Fajardo. The film follows a Union soldier-turned-drifter and his companion, a mixed-race prostitute, who become embroiled in a bitter, destructive feud between a Ku Klux Klan-esque gang of Confederate Red Shirts and a band of Mexican revolutionaries. Intended to capitalize on and rival the success of Sergio Leone's A Fistful of Dollars, Corbucci's film is, like Leone's, considered to be a loose, unofficial adaptation of Akira Kurosawa's Yojimbo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>