<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Tomás Milián</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Tomás Milián</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Compañeros]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Compañeros is a 1970 Zapata Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci. The film stars Franco Nero, Tomas Milian, Jack Palance and Fernando Rey. The soundtrack for the film was written by Ennio Morricone, and the orchestra was conducted by Bruno Nicolai.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sonny and Jed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sonny-and-jed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sonny and Jed is a 1972 Italian Spaghetti Western film about a sheriff's relentless effort to stop a robber and his girlfriend. The film was directed by Sergio Corbucci and is noted for its music, scored by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sonny-and-jed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The White, the Yellow, and the Black]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-white,-the-yellow,-and-the-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The White, the Yellow, and the Black, also known as Samurai and Shoot First... Ask Questions Later, is a 1975 Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-white,-the-yellow,-and-the-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse is a 1975 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Lucio Fulci and starring Fabio Testi, Tomas Milian and Michael J. Pollard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Sentence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Sentence is a 1968 spaghetti western directed by Mario Lanfranchi and starring Richard Conte.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Viva Cangaceiro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/viva-cangaceiro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Viva Cangaceiro is a Brazilian themed spaghetti western movie co-produced by Spain and Italy and directed by Giovanni Fago as his third and last spaghetti western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/viva-cangaceiro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tepepa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tepepa, also known as Blood and Guns, is an Italian epic Zapata Western film starring Tomas Milian and Orson Welles. The film was directed by Giulio Petroni. It was co-produced with Spain, where the film was released with the title Tepepa... Viva La Revolución.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Life Is Tough]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/life-is-tough/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Life Is Tough, Eh Providence? is a 1972 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Giulio Petroni. The film was a box office success and generated an immediate sequel, Here We Go Again, Eh Providence?.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/life-is-tough/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>