<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Franco Giraldi</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Franco Giraldi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors is a Technicolor 1966 Italian spaghetti western. It is the directorial debut film of Franco Giraldi, who was Sergio Leone's assistant in A Fistful of Dollars. The film gained a great commercial success and generated an immediate sequel, Up the MacGregors! (1967), again directed by Giraldi, and a later sequel, More Dollars for the MacGregors (1970).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die is a 1968 Italian spaghetti western. It is the fourth and last western directed by Franco Giraldi. It was originally intended as being directed by Sergio Corbucci and the cast was to include also Raffaella Carrà and Renzo Palmer. The American version of the film was heavily cut and handled, including a different ending, and it lasts 16 minutes less than the original version.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugar Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sugar Colt is a 1966 Italian and Spanish spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi, produced by Franco Cittadini and Stenio Fiorentini, written by Sandro Continenza, Augusto Finocchi, Giuseppe Mangione and Fernando Di Leo, composed by Luis Enríquez Bacalov, filmed by Alejandro Ulloa and starred by Jack Betts, Joaquín Parra, Soledad Miranda, Georges Rigaud, Antonio Padilla, Giuliano Raffaelli and Hunt Powers. It is the Giraldi's second film after Seven Guns for the MacGregors. The film represents the cinematographical debut for Jack Betts, here credited as Hunt Powers, and it is also Erno Crisa's last film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Die 7 Pistolen des McGregor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-7-pistolen-des-mcgregor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Die 7 Pistolen des McGregor ist ein Italowestern von Franco Giraldi. Deutsche Erstaufführung war am 5. August 1966. Im Jahr darauf erschien die Fortsetzung Eine Kugel für Mac Gregor.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-7-pistolen-des-mcgregor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Eine Kugel für Mac Gregor]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/eine-kugel-für-mac-gregor/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Eine Kugel für Mac Gregor ist ein komödiantischer Italowestern aus italienisch-spanischer Koproduktion, den Franco Giraldi 1966 als Fortsetzung von Die 7 Pistolen des McGregor inszenierte. Die deutschsprachige Erstaufführung erfolgte am 14. Juni 1968. Alternativtitel ist Auf den Sheriff schießt man nicht.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/eine-kugel-für-mac-gregor/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mehr tot als lebendig]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mehr-tot-als-lebendig/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mehr tot als lebendig ist ein Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1968. Deutschsprachige Erstaufführung des von Franco Giraldi mit US-amerikanischen Stars in den Hauptrollen inszenierten Filmes war der 3. Juli 1968.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mehr-tot-als-lebendig/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rocco – der Mann mit den zwei Gesichtern]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/rocco-–-der-mann-mit-den-zwei-gesichtern/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Rocco – der Mann mit den zwei Gesichtern ist ein Italowestern von Franco Giraldi aus dem Jahr 1966. Der von etlichen Kritikern gelobte Film, ein seltener Kriminal-Western, wurde im deutschsprachigen Raum am 14. Mai 1968 erstaufgeführt und in der DDR als Kavallerie in Not mit anderer Synchronisation gezeigt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/rocco-–-der-mann-mit-den-zwei-gesichtern/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>