<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » José Torres</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » José Torres</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tepepa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tepepa, also known as Blood and Guns, is an Italian epic Zapata Western film starring Tomas Milian and Orson Welles. The film was directed by Giulio Petroni. It was co-produced with Spain, where the film was released with the title Tepepa... Viva La Revolución.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perché uccidi ancora]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/perché-uccidi-ancora/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Perché uccidi ancora is a 1965 Italian western film adventure directed by José Antonio de la Loma and Edoardo Mulargia.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/perché-uccidi-ancora/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[... and called it the Holy Spirit]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/and-called-it-the-holy-spirit/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[He Was Called Holy Ghost is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western-comedy film written and directed by Roberto Mauri and starring Vassili Karis. It was followed by Return of the Holy Ghost (1972), still directed by Mauri and with Karis in the title role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/and-called-it-the-holy-spirit/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Degueyo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Degueyo is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giuseppe Vari.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[30 Winchester per El Diablo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/30-winchester-per-el-diablo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[30 Winchester per El Diablo is a 1965 Italian spaghetti western film directed and written by Gianfranco Baldanello. The film stars Carl Möhner and has occasionally been mistaken for a German western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/30-winchester-per-el-diablo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Preparati la bara!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django, Prepare a Coffin, alternatively titled Viva Django, is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film stars Terence Hill in the title role, which was previously played by Franco Nero in Sergio Corbucci's original film. Django, Prepare a Coffin is unique among the plethora of films which capitalized on Corbucci's in that it is not only a semi-official, legitimate follow-up, but was also originally intended to star Nero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Poker with Pistols]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/poker-with-pistols/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Poker with Pistols is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giuseppe Vari.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/poker-with-pistols/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play is a 1967 spaghetti western starring Gilbert Roland, Edd Byrnes and George Hilton. The film is directed by Enzo G. Castellari. The film is about a group of cowboys searching for gold, double-leading to double crosses as they continually change allegiances and get the upper hand only to be thwarted by fellow outlaws, mysterious insurance investigators and each other.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>