<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » José Torres</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » José Torres</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:48 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West is a 1964 Italian comedy western film directed by Giorgio Simonelli. Its stars Franco Franchi, Ciccio Ingrassia and Fernando Sancho.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sartana the Gravedigger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[I am Sartana, Your Angel of Death is a 1969 Italian Western film directed by Giuliano Carnimeo and starring Gianni Garko. The film is presented on some DVD reissues under its German title, Sartana - Töten war sein täglich Brot.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Degueyo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Degueyo is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giuseppe Vari.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Poker with Pistols]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/poker-with-pistols/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Poker with Pistols is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giuseppe Vari.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/poker-with-pistols/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tepepa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tepepa, also known as Blood and Guns, is an Italian epic Zapata Western film starring Tomas Milian and Orson Welles. The film was directed by Giulio Petroni. It was co-produced with Spain, where the film was released with the title Tepepa... Viva La Revolución.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tepepa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play is a 1967 spaghetti western starring Gilbert Roland, Edd Byrnes and George Hilton. The film is directed by Enzo G. Castellari. The film is about a group of cowboys searching for gold, double-leading to double crosses as they continually change allegiances and get the upper hand only to be thwarted by fellow outlaws, mysterious insurance investigators and each other.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Preparati la bara!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django, Prepare a Coffin, alternatively titled Viva Django, is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film stars Terence Hill in the title role, which was previously played by Franco Nero in Sergio Corbucci's original film. Django, Prepare a Coffin is unique among the plethora of films which capitalized on Corbucci's in that it is not only a semi-official, legitimate follow-up, but was also originally intended to star Nero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Perché uccidi ancora]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/perché-uccidi-ancora/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Perché uccidi ancora is a 1965 Italian western film adventure directed by José Antonio de la Loma and Edoardo Mulargia.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/perché-uccidi-ancora/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Five Man Army]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-five-man-army/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Five Man Army is a 1969 Italian Zapata Western film taking place during the Mexican Revolution.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-five-man-army/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>