<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Gianni Rizzo</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Gianni Rizzo</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/if-you-meet-sartana-pray-for-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death is a 1968 spaghetti western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. The film stars Gianni Garko, William Berger, Fernando Sancho and Klaus Kinski, and features a musical score by Piero Piccioni.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/if-you-meet-sartana-pray-for-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the second film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini. Yul Brynner takes over the lead role from Lee Van Cleef, who stars in the first and third films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Return of Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Return of Sabata is a 1971 Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. The third film in The Sabata Trilogy, it features the return of Lee Van Cleef as the title character, which he had played in the first film, Sabata, but was replaced by Yul Brynner in the second film, Adiós, Sabata, due to a scheduling conflict. Return of Sabata was listed in the 1978 book The Fifty Worst Films of All Time.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata ist ein Italo-Western aus dem Jahr 1969. Die Regie führte Gianfranco Parolini, als ausführender Produzent war Alberto Grimaldi verantwortlich. Die deutsche Erstaufführung war am 2. Mai 1970.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sartana – Bete um Deinen Tod]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sartana-bete-um-deinen-tod/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana – Bete um Deinen Tod aus dem Jahr 1968 ist ein Italo-Western des italienischen Regisseurs Gianfranco Parolini unter seinem Pseudonym Frank Kramer. Die deutschsprachige Erstaufführung erfolgte am 22. August 1969.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sartana-bete-um-deinen-tod/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adios, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adios, Sabata ist ein Italo-Western, dem der Sabata-Stempel zur besseren Vermarktung erst nach Drehschluss aufgedrückt wurde. Im Original heißt der Held Indio Black.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Von Angesicht zu Angesicht]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-angesicht-zu-angesicht/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Von Angesicht zu Angesicht ist ein 1967 von Sergio Sollima gedrehter Italowestern mit Tomás Milián, Gian Maria Volontè und William Berger in den Hauptrollen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-angesicht-zu-angesicht/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>