<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Gian Maria Volonté</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Gian Maria Volonté</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volonté as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood in his first leading role, alongside Gian Maria Volonté, Marianne Koch, Wolfgang Lukschy, Sieghardt Rupp, José Calvo, Antonio Prieto, and Joseph Egger. The film, an international co-production between Italy, West Germany, and Spain, was filmed on a low budget, and Eastwood was paid $15,000 for his role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Bullet for the General]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-bullet-for-the-general/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Bullet for the General is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Damiano Damiani starring Gian Maria Volonté, Lou Castel, Klaus Kinski and Martine Beswick. The film tells the story of El Chuncho, a bandit, and Bill Tate, who is a counter-revolutionary in Mexico. Chuncho soon learns that social revolution is more important than mere money.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-bullet-for-the-general/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>