<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Woody Strode</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Woody Strode</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boot Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Boot Hill is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Terence Hill and Bud Spencer. This film is the last one in a trilogy that started with God Forgives... I Don't! (1967), followed by Ace High (1968).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keoma]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Keoma is a 1976 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Franco Nero. It is frequently regarded as one of the better 'twilight' Spaghetti Westerns, being one of the last films of its genre, and is known for its incorporation of newer cinematic techniques of the time and its vocal soundtrack by Guido & Maurizio De Angelis.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chuck Moll]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chuck-moll/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chuck Moll is a 1970 Italian spaghetti western. The film represents the directorial debut of Enzo Barboni, who was, until then, a respected cinematographer. He replaced Ferdinando Baldi, who was fired by the producer Manolo Bolognini because of his insistence in wanting to engage the actress Annabella Incontrera in the role of Sheila.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chuck-moll/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:39 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>