<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Riccardo Pizzuti</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Riccardo Pizzuti</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Degueyo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Degueyo is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giuseppe Vari.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/degueyo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ace High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ace High is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and written by Giuseppe Colizzi and starring Terence Hill, Bud Spencer and Eli Wallach. The film is the second in a trilogy started with God Forgives... I Don't! and ended with Boot Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django Shoots First]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-shoots-first/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[

Django Shoots First is an Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Alberto De Martino.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-shoots-first/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man of the East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man of the East is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo Barboni starring Terence Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film written and directed by Enzo Barboni and produced by Italo Zingarelli. The film stars Terence Hill and Bud Spencer as two brothers, Trinity and Bambino, who help defend a Mormon settlement from Mexican bandits and the henchman of the land-grabbing Major Harriman. It was filmed on location in Lazio, Italy, with financial backing from West Film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keoma]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Keoma is a 1976 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Franco Nero. It is frequently regarded as one of the better 'twilight' Spaghetti Westerns, being one of the last films of its genre, and is known for its incorporation of newer cinematic techniques of the time and its vocal soundtrack by Guido & Maurizio De Angelis.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[W Django!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/w-django!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[W Django! is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Edoardo Mulargia and starring Anthony Steffen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/w-django!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>