<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Tonino Valerii</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Tonino Valerii</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name is Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[My Name Is Nobody is a 1973 western comedy film starring Terence Hill and Henry Fonda. The film was directed by Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die is a 1972 Technicolor Italian spaghetti western movie starring James Coburn, Bud Spencer and Telly Savalas.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Per il gusto di uccidere]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/per-il-gusto-di-uccidere/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Per il gusto di uccidere is the 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film debut directed by Tonino Valerii. It is also the first film to use the camera system known as 2P. It was filmed in Almería. It is produced by Francesco Genesi, Vincenzo Genesi, Daniele Senatore, Stefano Melpignano and Jose Lopez Moreno, scored by Nico Massi and edited by Rosa G. Salgado.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/per-il-gusto-di-uccidere/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mein Name ist Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mein-name-ist-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mein Name ist Nobody ist ein Italowestern mit einigen humorvollen Elementen von Tonino Valerii nach einer Idee von Sergio Leone. Die italienisch-deutsch-französische Koproduktion stammt aus dem Jahr 1973.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mein-name-ist-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blutiges Blei]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/blutiges-blei/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Blutiges Blei ist ein Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1969, eines von fünf Genrewerken des italienischen Regisseurs Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/blutiges-blei/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sie verkaufen den Tod]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sie-verkaufen-den-tod/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sie verkaufen den Tod ist ein Bürgerkriegswestern mit Bud Spencer und James Coburn in den Hauptrollen. Der Film wurde später mit dem Titel Der Dicke und das Warzenschwein in einer auf Komödie getrimmten Fassung herausgebracht. Erstmals in Kinos des deutschsprachigen Raumes lief er am 27. Dezember 1972.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/sie-verkaufen-den-tod/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lanky Fellow – Der einsame Rächer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lanky-fellow-–-der-einsame-rächer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Lanky Fellow – Der einsame Rächer ist ein Italowestern aus italienisch-spanischer Koproduktion, in dem Craig Hill unter der Regie von Tonino Valerii die Titelrolle spielt. Der Film wurde am 25. April 1967 im deutschsprachigen Raum erstaufgeführt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lanky-fellow-–-der-einsame-rächer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Tod ritt dienstags]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-ritt-dienstags/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Tod ritt dienstags ist ein Italowestern des italienischen Regisseurs Tonino Valerii aus dem Jahr 1967 nach einem Roman von Ron Barker.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-ritt-dienstags/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>