<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » George Rigaud</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » George Rigaud</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugar Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sugar Colt is a 1966 Italian and Spanish spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi, produced by Franco Cittadini and Stenio Fiorentini, written by Sandro Continenza, Augusto Finocchi, Giuseppe Mangione and Fernando Di Leo, composed by Luis Enríquez Bacalov, filmed by Alejandro Ulloa and starred by Jack Betts, Joaquín Parra, Soledad Miranda, Georges Rigaud, Antonio Padilla, Giuliano Raffaelli and Hunt Powers. It is the Giraldi's second film after Seven Guns for the MacGregors. The film represents the cinematographical debut for Jack Betts, here credited as Hunt Powers, and it is also Erno Crisa's last film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors is a Technicolor 1966 Italian spaghetti western. It is the directorial debut film of Franco Giraldi, who was Sergio Leone's assistant in A Fistful of Dollars. The film gained a great commercial success and generated an immediate sequel, Up the MacGregors! (1967), again directed by Giraldi, and a later sequel, More Dollars for the MacGregors (1970).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Texican]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Texican is a Technicolor 1966 Techniscope film produced and written by John C. Champion and directed by Lesley Selander. It is a paella western remake of their 1948 film Panhandle adapted for the persona of Audie Murphy that featured Broderick Crawford as the heavy. The film was retitled Ringo il Texano in Italy to coincide with the popularity of the Ringo spaghetti western film series.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Stranger and the Gunfighter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[1974 film by Antonio Margheriti]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-stranger-and-the-gunfighter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sundance and the Kid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sundance-and-the-kid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sundance and the Kid is the American release title of Vivi o, preferibilmente, morti, a 1969 Spaghetti Western comedy directed by Duccio Tessari and starring Giuliano Gemma, Nino Benvenuti, and 
Sydne Rome. The film is also known as Alive or Preferably Dead and Sundance Cassidy and Butch the Kid.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sundance-and-the-kid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cipolla Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/cipolla-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Cry, Onion! is a 1975 Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. It is openly comedic and parodic.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/cipolla-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Coffin for the Sheriff]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-coffin-for-the-sheriff/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Coffin for the Sheriff  is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Mario Caiano and starring Anthony Steffen, Eduardo Fajardo, Fulvia Franco, George Rigaud and Armando Calvo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-coffin-for-the-sheriff/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gatling Gun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gatling-gun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gatling Gun is a 1968 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Paolo Bianchini and starring Robert Woods.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gatling-gun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>