<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Gino Pernice</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Gino Pernice</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Compañeros]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Compañeros is a 1970 Zapata Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci. The film stars Franco Nero, Tomas Milian, Jack Palance and Fernando Rey. The soundtrack for the film was written by Ennio Morricone, and the orchestra was conducted by Bruno Nicolai.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Minnesota Clay]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/minnesota-clay/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Minnesota Clay is a 1964 Italian/French/Spanish international co-production spaghetti western directed by Sergio Corbucci.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/minnesota-clay/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Hellbenders]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-hellbenders/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Hellbenders is a 1967 Spaghetti Western directed by Sergio Corbucci.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-hellbenders/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rita of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Rita of the West, is a 1967 Italian musicarello-spaghetti western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gli specialisti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-specialisti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Specialist, also known as Specialists and Drop Them or I'll Shoot, is a 1969 Spaghetti Western co-written and directed by Sergio Corbucci. It was co-produced with West Germany and France and was released in France under the title Le spécialiste and in Germany with the title Fahrt zur Hölle, ihr Halunken. The title is probably intended to partner the previous Corbucci western, The Mercenary.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-specialisti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci, starring Franco Nero as the title character alongside Loredana Nusciak, José Bódalo, Ángel Álvarez and Eduardo Fajardo. The film follows a Union soldier-turned-drifter and his companion, a mixed-race prostitute, who become embroiled in a bitter, destructive feud between a Ku Klux Klan-esque gang of Confederate Red Shirts and a band of Mexican revolutionaries. Intended to capitalize on and rival the success of Sergio Leone's A Fistful of Dollars, Corbucci's film is, like Leone's, considered to be a loose, unofficial adaptation of Akira Kurosawa's Yojimbo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>