<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Karl Otto Alberty</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Karl Otto Alberty</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oklahoma John]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oklahoma-john/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Oklahoma John also known as Ranch of the Ruthless or The Man from Oklahoma is a Spanish, German and 1965 Italian international co-production western film directed by Jaime Jesús Balcázar and Roberto Bianchi Montero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oklahoma-john/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oklahoma John – Der Sheriff von Rio Rojo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/oklahoma-john-–-der-sheriff-von-rio-rojo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Oklahoma John – Der Sheriff von Rio Rojo ist ein früher, 1964, in italienisch-spanisch-deutscher Koproduktion hergestellter Italowestern. Er war im deutschsprachigen Raum erstmals am 5. Juni 1966 in leicht gekürzter Form zu sehen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/oklahoma-john-–-der-sheriff-von-rio-rojo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Tod ritt dienstags]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-ritt-dienstags/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Tod ritt dienstags ist ein Italowestern des italienischen Regisseurs Tonino Valerii aus dem Jahr 1967 nach einem Roman von Ron Barker.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-ritt-dienstags/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>