<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Livio Lorenzon</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Livio Lorenzon</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Buckaroo: The Winchester Does Not Forgive]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/buckaroo:-the-winchester-does-not-forgive/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Buckaroo: The Winchester Does Not Forgive is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Adelchi Bianchi and starring Dean Reed.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/buckaroo:-the-winchester-does-not-forgive/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ace High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ace High is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and written by Giuseppe Colizzi and starring Terence Hill, Bud Spencer and Eli Wallach. The film is the second in a trilogy started with God Forgives... I Don't! and ended with Boot Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[La sceriffa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-sceriffa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[La sceriffa is a 1959 Italian Western comedy in black-and-white, directed by Roberto Bianchi Montero. It stars Italian comedy star Ugo Tognazzi. It is considered one of the earliest Spaghetti Western films. It was released on 16 August 1959. The film starred several comedians and spawned a number of western comedies which followed.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-sceriffa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Rita of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Rita of the West, is a 1967 Italian musicarello-spaghetti western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/rita-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>