<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » John Bartha</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » John Bartha</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sartana the Gravedigger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[I am Sartana, Your Angel of Death is a 1969 Italian Western film directed by Giuliano Carnimeo and starring Gianni Garko. The film is presented on some DVD reissues under its German title, Sartana - Töten war sein täglich Brot.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-the-gravedigger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Seven from Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-seven-from-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Seven from Texas is a 1964 Spanish-Italian western film directed by Joaquín Luis Romero Marchent. It was shown as part of a retrospective on Spaghetti Western at the 64th Venice International Film Festival.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-seven-from-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kill Them All and Come Back Alone]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/kill-them-all-and-come-back-alone/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Kill Them All and Come Back Alone is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. It stars American actors Chuck Connors and Frank Wolff, and features a film score by Francesco De Masi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/kill-them-all-and-come-back-alone/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Dirty Outlaws]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-dirty-outlaws/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Dirty Outlaws, also known as Big Ripoff, King of the West and The Desperado, is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western starring Andrea Giordana.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-dirty-outlaws/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Solo contro tutti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/solo-contro-tutti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Jesse James' Kid is a 1965 Spanish-Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Antonio del Amo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/solo-contro-tutti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man of the East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man of the East is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo Barboni starring Terence Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[His Name Was King]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[His Name Was King is a 1971 Italian Western film directed by Giancarlo Romitelli and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/his-name-was-king/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Massacre Time]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/massacre-time/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Massacre Time is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Franco Nero and George Hilton. The film was released in the United States originally as The Brute and the Beast.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/massacre-time/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>