<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Ennio Morricone</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Ennio Morricone</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Mario Gariazzo and starring Ty Hardin, Rossano Brazzi and Craig Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Compañeros]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Compañeros is a 1970 Zapata Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci. The film stars Franco Nero, Tomas Milian, Jack Palance and Fernando Rey. The soundtrack for the film was written by Ennio Morricone, and the orchestra was conducted by Bruno Nicolai.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors is a Technicolor 1966 Italian spaghetti western. It is the directorial debut film of Franco Giraldi, who was Sergio Leone's assistant in A Fistful of Dollars. The film gained a great commercial success and generated an immediate sequel, Up the MacGregors! (1967), again directed by Giraldi, and a later sequel, More Dollars for the MacGregors (1970).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe (Italian: Un genio, due compari, un pollo is a 1975 spaghetti western comedy film directed by Damiano Damiani and Sergio Leone, who directed the opening scene.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!, also known as A Fistful of Dynamite and Once Upon a Time in… the Revolution, is a 1971 Italian epic Zapata Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Leone and starring Rod Steiger, James Coburn and Romolo Valli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name is Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[My Name Is Nobody is a 1973 comedy spaghetti western starring Terence Hill and Henry Fonda. The film was directed by Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Navajo Joe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/navajo-joe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Navajo Joe is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film, directed by Sergio Corbucci, and stars Burt Reynolds as the titular Navajo Indian who opposes a group of bandits responsible for killing his tribe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/navajo-joe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sonny and Jed]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sonny-and-jed/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sonny and Jed is a 1972 Italian Spaghetti Western film about a sheriff's relentless effort to stop a robber and his girlfriend. The film was directed by Sergio Corbucci and is noted for its music, scored by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sonny-and-jed/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>