<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Tomás Blanco</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Tomás Blanco</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Heroes of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/heroes-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Heroes of the West is a 1963 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Steno.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/heroes-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr ist ein Italowestern von Sergio Leone aus dem Jahr 1965, der als Nachfolger des Films Für eine Handvoll Dollar entstand. Er ist der zweite Teil der Dollar-Trilogie von Leone. In der Hauptrolle ist wiederum Clint Eastwood zu sehen, der sich in der Rolle eines Kopfgeldjägers mit dem von Lee Van Cleef gespielten Colonel Mortimer zu einem unschlagbaren Team zusammenrauft.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gli eroi del West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/gli-eroi-del-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Gli eroi del West ist eine im deutschen Sprachraum nicht aufgeführte Western-Parodie unter der Regie von Steno, die 1963 entstand.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/gli-eroi-del-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>