<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Nino Vingelli</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Nino Vingelli</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars Less]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-less/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars Less is a 1966 Italian comedy film parody of For a Few Dollars More directed by Mario Mattoli and starring Lando Buzzanca. It was Mattoli's final film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-less/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny Oro]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-oro/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ringo and His Golden Pistol is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci and starring Mark Damon.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-oro/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die is a 1968 Italian spaghetti western. It is the fourth and last western directed by Franco Giraldi. It was originally intended as being directed by Sergio Corbucci and the cast was to include also Raffaella Carrà and Renzo Palmer. The American version of the film was heavily cut and handled, including a different ending, and it lasts 16 minutes less than the original version.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hercules and the Treasure of the Incas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hercules-and-the-treasure-of-the-incas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Hercules and the Treasure of the Incas is a 1964 film written and directed by Piero Pierotti and starring Alan Steel. Originally conceived as a peplum film, given the contemporary success of A Fistful of Dollars, it was turned into a western film during the shootings, resulting in a bizarre crossover between the two genres.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hercules-and-the-treasure-of-the-incas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>