<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » José Calvo</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » José Calvo</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Thousand Dollars on the Black]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-thousand-dollars-on-the-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[

Blood at Sundown is a Spaghetti Western film directed by Alberto Cardone. The picture marks the first appearance of the character Sartana, played by Gianni Garko. It is not, however considered an "official" Sartana film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-thousand-dollars-on-the-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oklahoma John]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oklahoma-john/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Oklahoma John also known as Ranch of the Ruthless or The Man from Oklahoma is a Spanish, German and 1965 Italian international co-production western film directed by Jaime Jesús Balcázar and Roberto Bianchi Montero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oklahoma-john/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride is a 1971 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Aldo Florio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shoot Twice]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/shoot-twice/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Shoot Twice is a 1969 Italian Western film directed by Nando Cicero and starring Klaus Kinski and Antonio Sabàto. The film is also known as Twice a Judas.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/shoot-twice/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For One Thousand Dollars Per Day]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-one-thousand-dollars-per-day/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For One Thousand Dollars Per Day is a 1966 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Silvio Amadio. The title song ""My Gun is Fast" is performed by Bobby Solo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-one-thousand-dollars-per-day/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Stranger in Paso Bravo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-stranger-in-paso-bravo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Stranger in Paso Bravo is a 1968 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Salvatore Rosso. It was the first and only film directed by Rosso, who had previously been assistant of a number of directors, notably Pietro Germi. The film was remade in 1969 by Antonio Margheriti as And God Said to Cain; despite being the same story and having the main characters sharing the same names, the two films list different screenwriters. The film underperformed at the Italian box office, grossing only 34 million lire.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-stranger-in-paso-bravo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas, also known as Gunfight at Red Sands and Gringo, is a 1963 Italian/Spanish international co-production directed by Ricardo Blasco and Mario Caiano, and produced by Albert Band as his first spaghetti western. It was also the first Western to feature a score by Ennio Morricone and the second spaghetti western to star Richard Harrison.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Extra Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-extra-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Extra Dollars, also known as Fort Yuma Gold and Die Now, Pay Later, is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Ferroni.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-extra-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>