<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Giorgio Papi</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Giorgio Papi</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas, also known as Gunfight at Red Sands and Gringo, is a 1963 Italian/Spanish international co-production directed by Ricardo Blasco and Mario Caiano, and produced by Albert Band as his first spaghetti western. It was also the first Western to feature a score by Ennio Morricone and the second spaghetti western to star Richard Harrison.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood in his first leading role, alongside Gian Maria Volontè, Marianne Koch, Wolfgang Lukschy, Sieghardt Rupp, José Calvo, Antonio Prieto, and Joseph Egger. The film, an international co-production between Italy, West Germany, and Spain, was filmed on a low budget, and Eastwood was paid $15,000 for his role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Le pistole non discutono]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/le-pistole-non-discutono/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Bullets Don't Argue is a 1964 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Mario Caiano. The film was produced by Jolly Film back to back with Sergio Leone's A Fistful of Dollars, but with a more expensive budget and in anticipation of a greater success than the Leone's film, especially because at the time Rod Cameron was better known than Clint Eastwood.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/le-pistole-non-discutono/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>