<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Aldo Sambrell</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Aldo Sambrell</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell, in the original Italian known as Vivo per la tua morte, is a 1968 film directed by Camillo Bazzoni. It is based on the novel Judas Gun by Gordon D. Shirreffs. The film was bodybuilder Steve Reeves' final film prior to his retirement. Reeves, who turned down the lead of A Fistful of Dollars financed and co-wrote the film himself upon seeing the successful box office returns of the Clint Eastwood spaghetti westerns at the time. The film did poorly and Reeves retired from filmmaking that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!, also known as A Fistful of Dynamite and Once Upon a Time in… the Revolution, is a 1971 Italian epic Zapata Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Leone and starring Rod Steiger, James Coburn and Romolo Valli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[All'ombra di una colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/all'ombra-di-una-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[In a Colt's Shadow is a 1965 Italian spaghetti western film directed and written by Giovanni Grimaldi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/all'ombra-di-una-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Apache Fury]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/apache-fury/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Apache Fury is a 1964 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western directed and co-written by José María Elorrieta. It was based on a novel by Eduardo Guzman.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/apache-fury/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[La magnifica sfida]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-magnifica-sfida/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Falcon of the Desert or is a 1965 Italian adventure film directed by Miguel Lluch.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/la-magnifica-sfida/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volonté as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns, also known as Arizona Lets Fly and Kill Everybody and If You Gotta Shoot Someone... Bang! Bang!, is a 1970 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Martino and starring Anthony Steffen. The feature film debut of Martino after a series of documentary films, it is the sequel of Arizona Colt, with Steffen replacing Giuliano Gemma in the title role and with only Roberto Camardiel reprising his role from the previous film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>