<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Tonino Valerii</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Tonino Valerii</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:30 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name is Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[My Name Is Nobody is a 1973 comedy spaghetti western starring Terence Hill and Henry Fonda. The film was directed by Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die is a 1972 Technicolor Italian spaghetti western movie starring James Coburn, Bud Spencer and Telly Savalas.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Per il gusto di uccidere]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/per-il-gusto-di-uccidere/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Per il gusto di uccidere is the 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film debut directed by Tonino Valerii. It is also the first film to use the camera system known as 2P. It was filmed in Almería. It is produced by Francesco Genesi, Vincenzo Genesi, Daniele Senatore, Stefano Melpignano and Jose Lopez Moreno, scored by Nico Massi and edited by Rosa G. Salgado.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/per-il-gusto-di-uccidere/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:27 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>