<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Clint Eastwood</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Clint Eastwood</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volonté as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood in his first leading role, alongside Gian Maria Volonté, Marianne Koch, Wolfgang Lukschy, Sieghardt Rupp, José Calvo, Antonio Prieto, and Joseph Egger. The film, an international co-production between Italy, West Germany, and Spain, was filmed on a low budget, and Eastwood was paid $15,000 for his role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Zwei glorreiche Halunken]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/zwei-glorreiche-halunken/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Zwei glorreiche Halunken ist ein Spielfilm aus dem Jahr 1966. Er entstand unter der Regie von Sergio Leone und gilt als Klassiker des Italowestern, nach Für eine Handvoll Dollar und Für ein paar Dollar mehr der dritte Teil von Leones „Dollar-Trilogie“, in der jeweils Clint Eastwood eine der Hauptrollen spielt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/zwei-glorreiche-halunken/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Für ein paar Dollar mehr ist ein Italowestern von Sergio Leone aus dem Jahr 1965, der als Nachfolger des Films Für eine Handvoll Dollar entstand. Er ist der zweite Teil der Dollar-Trilogie von Leone. In der Hauptrolle ist wiederum Clint Eastwood zu sehen, der sich in der Rolle eines Kopfgeldjägers mit dem von Lee Van Cleef gespielten Colonel Mortimer zu einem unschlagbaren Team zusammenrauft.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-ein-paar-dollar-mehr/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Für eine Handvoll Dollar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-eine-handvoll-dollar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Für eine Handvoll Dollar ist ein Italowestern von Sergio Leone aus dem Jahr 1964. Es ist der erste Teil der sogenannten Dollar-Trilogie Leones und führt Clint Eastwood in der Rolle eines mysteriösen Fremden in den mexikanischen Wüstenort San Miguel. Dort wird er nicht nur mit mitleidloser Brutalität, sondern auch mit dem Tod konfrontiert. Tragende Rollen sind mit Marianne Koch, Gian Maria Volonté, José Calvo, Wolfgang Lukschy und Sieghardt Rupp besetzt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/für-eine-handvoll-dollar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>