<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Roberto Camardiel</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Roberto Camardiel</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós gringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós gringo is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giorgio Stegani. Its stars Giuliano Gemma and was co produced between Italy, Spain and France. On release in the United States, nearly all of the cast members and production team had their names changed for the English audience. A major success, it was the 4th highest grossing picture of the year in Italy.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Solo contro tutti]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/solo-contro-tutti/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Jesse James' Kid is a 1965 Spanish-Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Antonio del Amo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/solo-contro-tutti/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Johnny West il mancino]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-west-il-mancino/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Left Handed Johnny West is a 1965 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/johnny-west-il-mancino/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns, also known as Arizona Lets Fly and Kill Everybody and If You Gotta Shoot Someone... Bang! Bang!, is a 1970 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Martino and starring Anthony Steffen. The feature film debut of Martino after a series of documentary films, it is the sequel of Arizona Colt, with Steffen replacing Giuliano Gemma in the title role and with only Roberto Camardiel reprising his role from the previous film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django Kill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-kill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django Kill... If You Live, Shoot! is a film directed by Giulio Questi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-kill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Big Gundown is a Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Sollima, and starring Lee Van Cleef and Tomas Milian.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Train for Durango]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/train-for-durango/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Train for Durango is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Mario Caiano.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/train-for-durango/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Colt, also known as The Man from Nowhere, is a Spaghetti Western directed by Michele Lupo and starring Giuliano Gemma, Fernando Sancho and Corinne Marchand.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>