<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Antón García Abril</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Antón García Abril</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:42 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pancho Villa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Pancho Villa is a 1972 American, British and Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Eugenio Martín. The film features Telly Savalas, Clint Walker, Chuck Connors and Anne Francis. Shot in Spain, this "brawling spectacle" has an often-overlooked light-comedy satirical facet, which to this day often confuses the viewers. The storyline was developed during the Vietnam War and reflected certain antiwar sentiments in an American society.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Savage Guns (1961 film)]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/savage-guns-(1961-film)/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Savage Guns is a 1961 Eurowestern film, an international co-production by British and Spanish producers. Based on a specially commissioned screenplay, The San Siado Killings, written by Peter R. Newman and directed by Michael Carreras, the film is credited as the first traditional Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/savage-guns-(1961-film)/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 20:11:40 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>