<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Bruno Corazzari</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Bruno Corazzari</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:47 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Drummer of Vengeance is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Mario Gariazzo and starring Ty Hardin, Rossano Brazzi and Craig Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/drummer-of-vengeance/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Giubbe rosse / Red Coats is a 1975 Italian adventure film co-written and directed by Joe D'Amato. It is part of a brief series of films that tried to market the commercial success of Lucio Fulci's White Fang presenting very similar plots and settings. D'Amato co-wrote the film with writer/actor Luigi Montefiori, who went on to star in a dozen or more D'Amato films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/giubbe-rosse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell, in the original Italian known as Vivo per la tua morte, is a 1968 film directed by Camillo Bazzoni. It is based on the novel Judas Gun by Gordon D. Shirreffs. The film was bodybuilder Steve Reeves' final film prior to his retirement. Reeves, who turned down the lead of A Fistful of Dollars financed and co-wrote the film himself upon seeing the successful box office returns of the Clint Eastwood spaghetti westerns at the time. The film did poorly and Reeves retired from filmmaking that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Terrible Day of the Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/terrible-day-of-the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Terrible Day of the Big Gundown is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/terrible-day-of-the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Belle Starr Story]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-belle-starr-story/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Belle Starr Story/Il mio corpo per un poker is a 1968 Italian made episodic Bonnie and Clyde type spaghetti western co-written and co-directed by Lina Wertmüller and starring Elsa Martinelli who also sings the title song. It is the only spaghetti western directed by a woman and one of the few which stars a woman in the title role. Wertmüller replaced after a few days Piero Cristofani, who was at his directorial debut.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-belle-starr-story/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the second film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini. Yul Brynner takes over the lead role from Lee Van Cleef, who stars in the first and third films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ace High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ace High is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and written by Giuseppe Colizzi and starring Terence Hill, Bud Spencer and Eli Wallach. The film is the second in a trilogy started with God Forgives... I Don't! and ended with Boot Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Four of the Apocalypse is a 1975 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Lucio Fulci and starring Fabio Testi, Tomas Milian and Michael J. Pollard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/four-of-the-apocalypse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Great Silence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Great Silence is a 1968 revisionist Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci. An Italian-French co-production, the film stars Jean-Louis Trintignant, Klaus Kinski, Vonetta McGee and Frank Wolff, with Luigi Pistilli, Mario Brega, Marisa Merlini and Carlo D'Angelo in supporting roles.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-great-silence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 02:34:45 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>