<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Eli Wallach</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Eli Wallach</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The White, the Yellow, and the Black]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-white,-the-yellow,-and-the-black/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The White, the Yellow, and the Black, also known as Samurai and Shoot First... Ask Questions Later, is a 1975 Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-white,-the-yellow,-and-the-black/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Ace High]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Ace High is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and written by Giuseppe Colizzi and starring Terence Hill, Bud Spencer and Eli Wallach. The film is the second in a trilogy started with God Forgives... I Don't! and ended with Boot Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/ace-high/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death is a 1971 Italian/Spanish/German international co-production spaghetti western/ action comedy film directed by Duccio Tessari. The film is mostly a send up of "political" Spaghetti Westerns, like A Professional Gun and Compañeros.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>