<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Romano Puppo</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Romano Puppo</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride is a 1971 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Aldo Florio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[China 9, Liberty 37 is an Italian-Spanish 1978 Western film directed by Monte Hellman, starring Warren Oates, Jenny Agutter, and Fabio Testi. Noted director Sam Peckinpah has a small, rare acting role. The film was shot in locations in Spain and Italy by cinematographer Giuseppe Rotunno. Pino Donaggio composed the musical score. The film had a very sparse theatrical release in the United States, and did not play in some cities until as late as 1984.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/china-9,-liberty-37/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gli uomini dal passo pesante]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-uomini-dal-passo-pesante/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Tramplers is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Albert Band and Mario Sequi based on the novel Guns of North Texas by Will Cook.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-uomini-dal-passo-pesante/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[California]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[California is a 1977 Italo-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Michele Lupo. The film was generally well received by critics and obtained a good commercial success at Italian box office.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Los Amigos]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/los-amigos/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Deaf Smith & Johnny Ears, also known as Los Amigos, is a 1973 Spaghetti Western film starring Anthony Quinn and Franco Nero in 1973. The film is loosely based on the life of Deaf Smith, with direction of Paolo Cavara.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/los-amigos/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Law]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Beyond the Law is a 1968 Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Stegani and starring Lee Van Cleef as Cudlip, Antonio Sabàto Sr. as Ben Novack and Gordon Mitchell as Burton. It was first distributed in the United States in 1971.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Big Gundown is a Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Sollima, and starring Lee Van Cleef and Tomas Milian.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>