<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Giorgio Stegani</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Giorgio Stegani</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós gringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós gringo is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giorgio Stegani. Its stars Giuliano Gemma and was co produced between Italy, Spain and France. On release in the United States, nearly all of the cast members and production team had their names changed for the English audience. A major success, it was the 4th highest grossing picture of the year in Italy.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós-gringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Beyond the Law]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Beyond the Law is a 1968 Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Stegani and starring Lee Van Cleef as Cudlip, Antonio Sabàto Sr. as Ben Novack and Gordon Mitchell as Burton. It was first distributed in the United States in 1971.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/beyond-the-law/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adios Gringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios-gringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adios Gringo ist ein französisch-italienisch-spanischer Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1965 von Giorgio Stegani. Es ist ein früher Italowestern, welcher sich sehr an den amerikanischen Vorbildern orientiert. Die Geschichte ist an ein Buch von Heftautor Harry Whittington angelehnt. Der deutsche Titelsong wird von Jürgen Herbst gesungen; das Originallied von Fred Bongusto.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios-gringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Die letzte Rechnung zahlst du selbst]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-letzte-rechnung-zahlst-du-selbst/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Die letzte Rechnung zahlst du selbst ist ein Italowestern, den Giorgio Stegani unter dem Pseudonym George Finley inszenierte. Kinostart der gekürzten deutschen Fassung war am 30. August 1968.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/die-letzte-rechnung-zahlst-du-selbst/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>