<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Calisto Calisti</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Calisto Calisti</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:01 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the second film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini. Yul Brynner takes over the lead role from Lee Van Cleef, who stars in the first and third films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars Less]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-less/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars Less is a 1966 Italian comedy film parody of For a Few Dollars More directed by Mario Mattoli and starring Lando Buzzanca. It was Mattoli's final film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-less/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Big Gundown is a Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Sollima, and starring Lee Van Cleef and Tomas Milian.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauf um dein Leben]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lauf-um-dein-leben/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Lauf um dein Leben ist ein Italowestern von Regisseur Sergio Sollima aus dem Jahre 1968. Die Hauptrolle spielten Tomás Milián und Donald O’Brien. Von anderen Filmen des Genres hebt er sich insbesondere durch seine politische Komponente ab, die auch in den beiden anderen Western Sollimas, Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre und Von Angesicht zu Angesicht, erkennbar ist.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lauf-um-dein-leben/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adios, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adios, Sabata ist ein Italo-Western, dem der Sabata-Stempel zur besseren Vermarktung erst nach Drehschluss aufgedrückt wurde. Im Original heißt der Held Indio Black.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/adios,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Irren ist tödlich]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/irren-ist-tödlich/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Irren ist tödlich ist eine italienische Italowestern-Komödie aus dem Jahr 1966. Die direkte Parodie auf Für ein paar Dollar mehr – der Originaltitel bedeutet „Für ein paar Dollar weniger“ – wurde von Mario Mattòli inszeniert und im deutschen Sprachraum erst 1988 im DFF erstmals gezeigt.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/irren-ist-tödlich/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-gehetzte-der-sierra-madre/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre ist ein von Sergio Sollima 1966 gedrehter Italowestern mit Lee Van Cleef und Tomás Milián in den Hauptrollen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-gehetzte-der-sierra-madre/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:58 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>