<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Enzo Fiermonte</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Enzo Fiermonte</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell, in the original Italian known as Vivo per la tua morte, is a 1968 film directed by Camillo Bazzoni. It is based on the novel Judas Gun by Gordon D. Shirreffs. The film was bodybuilder Steve Reeves' final film prior to his retirement. Reeves, who turned down the lead of A Fistful of Dollars financed and co-wrote the film himself upon seeing the successful box office returns of the Clint Eastwood spaghetti westerns at the time. The film did poorly and Reeves retired from filmmaking that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Those Dirty Dogs]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/those-dirty-dogs/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Those Dirty Dogs is a 1973 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Giuseppe Rosati and starring Gianni Garko and Stephen Boyd. The film was made in the later part of the spaghetti western boom. As such it features such latter-day genre elements as self-parody, guffaw humour, near-slapstick fight scenes, machine guns hidden in everyday household items, and bombastic villains.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/those-dirty-dogs/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Boot Hill]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Boot Hill is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film starring Terence Hill and Bud Spencer. This film is the last one in a trilogy that started with God Forgives... I Don't! (1967), followed by Ace High (1968).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/boot-hill/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man of the East]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man of the East is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo Barboni starring Terence Hill.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-of-the-east/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mannaja]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mannaja/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mannaja is an Italian 1977 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Martino. The main role, Blade, is played by Maurizio Merli. Other central roles are played by John Steiner, Sonja Jeannine, Donald O'Brien, Philippe Leroy and Martine Brochard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mannaja/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[California]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[California is a 1977 Italo-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Michele Lupo. The film was generally well received by critics and obtained a good commercial success at Italian box office.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film is a western adaptation of the Greek myth of Orestes, subject of three famous drama-plays by Aeschylus, Sophocles and Euripides. Ulrich P. Bruckner puts it among the "most interesting and most touching Spaghetti Westerns of the late sixties".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die is a 1968 Italian spaghetti western. It is the fourth and last western directed by Franco Giraldi. It was originally intended as being directed by Sergio Corbucci and the cast was to include also Raffaella Carrà and Renzo Palmer. The American version of the film was heavily cut and handled, including a different ending, and it lasts 16 minutes less than the original version.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Halleluja for Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[La più grande rapina del West is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Maurizio Lucidi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/halleluja-for-django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Bounty Killer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-bounty-killer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Ugly Ones is a 1966 Spanish-Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Eugenio Martín.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-bounty-killer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>