<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Víctor Israel</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Víctor Israel</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sugar Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sugar Colt is a 1966 Italian and Spanish spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi, produced by Franco Cittadini and Stenio Fiorentini, written by Sandro Continenza, Augusto Finocchi, Giuseppe Mangione and Fernando Di Leo, composed by Luis Enríquez Bacalov, filmed by Alejandro Ulloa and starred by Jack Betts, Joaquín Parra, Soledad Miranda, Georges Rigaud, Antonio Padilla, Giuliano Raffaelli and Hunt Powers. It is the Giraldi's second film after Seven Guns for the MacGregors. The film represents the cinematographical debut for Jack Betts, here credited as Hunt Powers, and it is also Erno Crisa's last film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sugar-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Seven Guns for the MacGregors is a Technicolor 1966 Italian spaghetti western. It is the directorial debut film of Franco Giraldi, who was Sergio Leone's assistant in A Fistful of Dollars. The film gained a great commercial success and generated an immediate sequel, Up the MacGregors! (1967), again directed by Giraldi, and a later sequel, More Dollars for the MacGregors (1970).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/seven-guns-for-the-macgregors/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Texican]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Texican is a Technicolor 1966 Techniscope film produced and written by John C. Champion and directed by Lesley Selander. It is a paella western remake of their 1948 film Panhandle adapted for the persona of Audie Murphy that featured Broderick Crawford as the heavy. The film was retitled Ringo il Texano in Italy to coincide with the popularity of the Ringo spaghetti western film series.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Compañeros]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Compañeros is a 1970 Zapata Western film directed by Sergio Corbucci. The film stars Franco Nero, Tomas Milian, Jack Palance and Fernando Rey. The soundtrack for the film was written by Ennio Morricone, and the orchestra was conducted by Bruno Nicolai.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/compañeros/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Long Live Your Death is a 1971 Italian/Spanish/German international co-production spaghetti western/ action comedy film directed by Duccio Tessari. The film is mostly a send up of "political" Spaghetti Westerns, like A Professional Gun and Compañeros.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/long-live-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Dollar Too Many]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-dollar-too-many/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[One Dollar Too Many is a 1968 Spaghetti Western feature film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Antonio Sabàto, John Saxon, and 
Frank Wolff.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-dollar-too-many/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Killer Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/killer-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Killer Adios is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Primo Zeglio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/killer-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>