<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Benito Stefanelli</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Benito Stefanelli</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:29 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!, also known as A Fistful of Dynamite and Once Upon a Time in… the Revolution, is a 1971 Italian epic Zapata Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Leone and starring Rod Steiger, James Coburn and Romolo Valli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[El Macho]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/el-macho/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[El Macho is a 1977 Italian-Argentine Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Marcello Andrei.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/el-macho/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Genius, Two Partners and a Dupe (Italian: Un genio, due compari, un pollo is a 1975 spaghetti western comedy film directed by Damiano Damiani and Sergio Leone, who directed the opening scene.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-genius,-two-partners-and-a-dupe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name is Nobody]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[My Name Is Nobody is a 1973 comedy spaghetti western starring Terence Hill and Henry Fonda. The film was directed by Tonino Valerii.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-nobody/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:42:28 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>