<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Umberto Di Grazia</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Umberto Di Grazia</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Hey Amigo! A Toast to Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hey-amigo!-a-toast-to-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Hey Amigo! A Toast to Your Death is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Paolo Bianchini and starring Wayde Preston.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/hey-amigo!-a-toast-to-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I Am Sartana, Trade Your Guns for a Coffin]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana's Here… Trade Your Pistol for a Coffin is a 1970 spaghetti western that is the third of the Sartana film series with George Hilton taking over the lead role from Gianni Garko. The film was shot in Italy and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-am-sartana,-trade-your-guns-for-a-coffin/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Find a Place to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/find-a-place-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Find a Place to Die (1968) is a spaghetti western starring Jeffrey Hunter and Pascale Petit. It was co-written and directed by Giuliano Carnimeo with sequences directed by Hugo Fregonese who also produced the film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/find-a-place-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Sentence]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Sentence is a 1968 spaghetti western directed by Mario Lanfranchi and starring Richard Conte.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-sentence/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Chuck Moll]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chuck-moll/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Chuck Moll is a 1970 Italian spaghetti western. The film represents the directorial debut of Enzo Barboni, who was, until then, a respected cinematographer. He replaced Ferdinando Baldi, who was fired by the producer Manolo Bolognini because of his insistence in wanting to engage the actress Annabella Incontrera in the role of Sheila.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/chuck-moll/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>