<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Conrado San Martín</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Conrado San Martín</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duck, You Sucker!, also known as A Fistful of Dynamite and Once Upon a Time in… the Revolution, is a 1971 Italian epic Zapata Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Leone and starring Rod Steiger, James Coburn and Romolo Valli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duck,-you-sucker!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[All'ombra di una colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/all'ombra-di-una-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[In a Colt's Shadow is a 1965 Italian spaghetti western film directed and written by Giovanni Grimaldi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/all'ombra-di-una-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Once Upon a Time in the West is a 1968 epic Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Henry Fonda, cast against type, as the villain, Charles Bronson as his nemesis, Claudia Cardinale as a newly widowed homesteader, and Jason Robards as a bandit. The screenplay was written by Sergio Donati and Leone, from a story by Dario Argento, Bernardo Bertolucci and Leone. The widescreen cinematography was by Tonino Delli Colli, and the acclaimed film score was by Ennio Morricone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/once-upon-a-time-in-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I lunghi giorni della vendetta]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-lunghi-giorni-della-vendetta/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[I lunghi giorni della vendetta is a 1967 Italian western film directed by Florestano Vancini. It is the only western directed by Vancini, here credited as Stan Vance. The film is a spaghetti western version of Alexandre Dumas' novel The Count of Monte Cristo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-lunghi-giorni-della-vendetta/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>