<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Lee Van Cleef</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Lee Van Cleef</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Storm Rider]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/storm-rider/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Grand Duel, also known as Storm Rider and The Big Showdown, is a 1972 Spaghetti Western film directed by Giancarlo Santi, who had previously worked as Sergio Leone's assistant director on The Good, the Bad and the Ugly and Once Upon a Time in the West. The film stars Lee Van Cleef as a sheriff who seeks justice for a man accused of murder.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/storm-rider/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[God's Gun]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/god's-gun/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[God's Gun is a 1976 Italian–Israeli Spaghetti Western filmed in Israel directed by Gianfranco Parolini and starring Lee Van Cleef. Jack Palance plays the head of a malicious group of bandits and Van Cleef plays a double-role of brothers: a priest and a reformed gunfighter determined to stop them.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/god's-gun/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Return of Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Return of Sabata is a 1971 Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. The third film in The Sabata Trilogy, it features the return of Lee Van Cleef as the title character, which he had played in the first film, Sabata, but was replaced by Yul Brynner in the second film, Adiós, Sabata, due to a scheduling conflict. Return of Sabata was listed in the 1978 book The Fifty Worst Films of All Time.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/return-of-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volonté as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bad Man's River]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Bad Man's River is a 1971 European comedy Spaghetti western directed by Eugenio Martín and starring Lee Van Cleef, James Mason, Gina Lollobrigida and Simón Andreu. Soundtrack was composed by Tony Duhig, Peter Jonfield, Glyn Havard and Waldo de los Ríos.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Take a Hard Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/take-a-hard-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[1975 film by Antonio Margheriti]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/take-a-hard-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 23:46:00 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>