<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Paolo Magalotti</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Paolo Magalotti</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:18 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[One Dollar Too Many]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-dollar-too-many/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[One Dollar Too Many is a 1968 Spaghetti Western feature film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Antonio Sabàto, John Saxon, and 
Frank Wolff.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/one-dollar-too-many/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fury of Johnny Kid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fury-of-johnny-kid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fury of Johnny Kid is a 1967 Italian-Spanish film directed by Gianni Puccini. The Italian and Spanish versions of the film have different ending. The film is a spaghetti western version of William Shakespeare's tragedy Romeo and Juliet.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fury-of-johnny-kid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[They Call Me Trinity is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film written and directed by Enzo Barboni and produced by Italo Zingarelli. The film stars Terence Hill and Bud Spencer as two brothers, Trinity and Bambino, who help defend a Mormon settlement from Mexican bandits and the henchman of the land-grabbing Major Harriman. It was filmed on location in Lazio, Italy, with financial backing from West Film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/they-call-me-trinity/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Up the MacGregors! is a 1967 Italian spaghetti western directed by Franco Giraldi. It is the immediate sequel of Seven Guns for the MacGregors, still directed by Giraldi. The film has the same cast as its predecessor except for Manuel Zarzo and Robert Woods, who refused the role due to his conflicts with the leading actress Agata Flori, the wife of producer Dario Sabatello.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/up-the-macgregors!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>