<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Franco Balducci</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Franco Balducci</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:23 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Long Ride from Hell, in the original Italian known as Vivo per la tua morte, is a 1968 film directed by Camillo Bazzoni. It is based on the novel Judas Gun by Gordon D. Shirreffs. The film was bodybuilder Steve Reeves' final film prior to his retirement. Reeves, who turned down the lead of A Fistful of Dollars financed and co-wrote the film himself upon seeing the successful box office returns of the Clint Eastwood spaghetti westerns at the time. The film did poorly and Reeves retired from filmmaking that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-long-ride-from-hell/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Doc, Hands of Steel]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/doc,-hands-of-steel/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Doc, Hands of Steel is a 1965 Spanish-Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Alfonso Balcázar.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/doc,-hands-of-steel/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Wanted]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Wanted is an Italian western film released in 1967. It was directed by Giorgio Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma, Teresa Gimpera, and Nello Pazzafini. Gemma made two more westerns directed by Ferroni, with similar plots, where his character likewise carried the first name "Gary".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/wanted/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Day of Anger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Day of Anger is a 1967 Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Tonino Valerii and starring Lee Van Cleef and Giuliano Gemma, and features a musical score by Riz Ortolani. The film credits the novel Der Tod ritt dienstags by Ron Barker as its basis, although Valerii and screenwriter Ernesto Gastaldi have attested that this credit was primarily included to appease the West German co-producers, and that although some scenes are partially borrowed from it, the film is not an adaptation of Becker's novel.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/day-of-anger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Time of Vultures]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/time-of-vultures/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Il tempo degli avvoltoi is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Nando Cicero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/time-of-vultures/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Sky Full of Stars for a Roof is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-sky-full-of-stars-for-a-roof/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Gli uomini dal passo pesante]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-uomini-dal-passo-pesante/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Tramplers is a 1965 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Albert Band and Mario Sequi based on the novel Guns of North Texas by Will Cook.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/gli-uomini-dal-passo-pesante/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Death Rides a Horse is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Giulio Petroni, written by Luciano Vincenzoni and starring Lee Van Cleef and John Phillip Law.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/death-rides-a-horse/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Preparati la bara!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django, Prepare a Coffin, alternatively titled Viva Django, is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film stars Terence Hill in the title role, which was previously played by Franco Nero in Sergio Corbucci's original film. Django, Prepare a Coffin is unique among the plethora of films which capitalized on Corbucci's in that it is not only a semi-official, legitimate follow-up, but was also originally intended to star Nero.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/preparati-la-bara!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Man Called Sledge]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-man-called-sledge/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Man Called Sledge is a 1970 Italian spaghetti western film starring James Garner in an extremely offbeat role as a grimly evil thief, and featuring Dennis Weaver, Claude Akins and Wayde Preston. The film was written by Vic Morrow and Frank Kowalski, and directed by Morrow in Techniscope.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-man-called-sledge/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:59:21 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>