<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » William Berger</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » William Berger</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:24:02 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[California]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[California is a 1977 Italo-Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Michele Lupo. The film was generally well received by critics and obtained a good commercial success at Italian box office.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/california/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Oggi a me... domani a te!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oggi-a-me...-domani-a-te!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Today We Kill... Tomorrow We Die! also known as Today It's Me... Tomorrow You!, is a 1968 Spaghetti Western film. It is the directorial debut of Tonino Cervi, who co-wrote the film with Dario Argento.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/oggi-a-me...-domani-a-te!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Una lunga fila di croci]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/una-lunga-fila-di-croci/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[No Room To Die is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Garrone.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/una-lunga-fila-di-croci/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/if-you-meet-sartana-pray-for-your-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death is a 1968 spaghetti western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. The film stars Gianni Garko, William Berger, Fernando Sancho and Klaus Kinski, and features a musical score by Piero Piccioni.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/if-you-meet-sartana-pray-for-your-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fasthand]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fasthand/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fasthand is a 1973 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Frank Bronston and starring Alan Steel, William Berger and Frank Braña.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fasthand/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sartana in the Valley of Death]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-in-the-valley-of-death/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sartana in the Valley of Death is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Roberto Mauri and starring William Berger.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sartana-in-the-valley-of-death/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Keoma]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Keoma is a 1976 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari and starring Franco Nero. It is frequently regarded as one of the better 'twilight' Spaghetti Westerns, being one of the last films of its genre, and is known for its incorporation of newer cinematic techniques of the time and its vocal soundtrack by Guido & Maurizio De Angelis.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/keoma/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django 2]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-2/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django Strikes Again is a 1987 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Nello Rossati. It is the only official sequel to Django.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django-2/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 01:23:59 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>