<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Sergio Sollima</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Sergio Sollima</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:07 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Big Gundown]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Big Gundown is a Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Sollima, and starring Lee Van Cleef and Tomas Milian.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-big-gundown/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Von Angesicht zu Angesicht]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-angesicht-zu-angesicht/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Von Angesicht zu Angesicht ist ein 1967 von Sergio Sollima gedrehter Italowestern mit Tomás Milián, Gian Maria Volontè und William Berger in den Hauptrollen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/von-angesicht-zu-angesicht/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Lauf um dein Leben]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lauf-um-dein-leben/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Lauf um dein Leben ist ein Italowestern von Regisseur Sergio Sollima aus dem Jahre 1968. Die Hauptrolle spielten Tomás Milián und Donald O’Brien. Von anderen Filmen des Genres hebt er sich insbesondere durch seine politische Komponente ab, die auch in den beiden anderen Western Sollimas, Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre und Von Angesicht zu Angesicht, erkennbar ist.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/lauf-um-dein-leben/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-gehetzte-der-sierra-madre/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Gehetzte der Sierra Madre ist ein von Sergio Sollima 1966 gedrehter Italowestern mit Lee Van Cleef und Tomás Milián in den Hauptrollen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-gehetzte-der-sierra-madre/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 23:55:05 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>