<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Ángel Álvarez</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Ángel Álvarez</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:17 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Navajo Joe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/navajo-joe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Navajo Joe is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film, directed by Sergio Corbucci, and stars Burt Reynolds as the titular Navajo Indian who opposes a group of bandits responsible for killing his tribe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/navajo-joe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fury of Johnny Kid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fury-of-johnny-kid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fury of Johnny Kid is a 1967 Italian-Spanish film directed by Gianni Puccini. The Italian and Spanish versions of the film have different ending. The film is a spaghetti western version of William Shakespeare's tragedy Romeo and Juliet.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fury-of-johnny-kid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the second film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini. Yul Brynner takes over the lead role from Lee Van Cleef, who stars in the first and third films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Requiem for a Gringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/requiem-for-a-gringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Requiem for a Gringo is a 1968 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Eugenio Martín and José Luis Merino and starring Lang Jeffries, Fernando Sancho and Femi Benussi. It is most known for the gore and psychedelic elements. It is the only western film of the Eurospy and peplum film genre star Lang Jeffries. The film is partially based on Masaki Kobayashi's film Harakiri.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/requiem-for-a-gringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die is a 1972 Technicolor Italian spaghetti western movie starring James Coburn, Bud Spencer and Telly Savalas.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Tres dólares de plomo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tres-dólares-de-plomo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tres dólares de plomo is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Pino Mercanti.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/tres-dólares-de-plomo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sting of the West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sting-of-the-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Tedeum is a 1972 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. The title role was initially offered to Tomas Milian, who eventually refused.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sting-of-the-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:15 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Django]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Django is a 1966 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed and co-written by Sergio Corbucci, starring Franco Nero as the title character alongside Loredana Nusciak, José Bódalo, Ángel Álvarez and Eduardo Fajardo. The film follows a Union soldier-turned-drifter and his companion, a mixed-race prostitute, who become embroiled in a bitter, destructive feud between a Ku Klux Klan-esque gang of Confederate Red Shirts and a band of Mexican revolutionaries. Intended to capitalize on and rival the success of Sergio Leone's A Fistful of Dollars, Corbucci's film is, like Leone's, considered to be a loose, unofficial adaptation of Akira Kurosawa's Yojimbo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/django/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Kopfgeld: Ein Dollar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/kopfgeld:-ein-dollar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Kopfgeld: Ein Dollar ist ein Italowestern von Sergio Corbucci aus dem Jahr 1966. Bei der spanisch-italienischen Koproduktion handelt sich um einen der seltenen Fälle, dass ein Indianer im Mittelpunkt der Handlung steht.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/kopfgeld:-ein-dollar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Glut der Sonne]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/glut-der-sonne/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Glut der Sonne ist ein italienisch-spanischer Spielfilm aus dem Jahr 1967 von Gianni Puccini. Es ist der einzige Italowestern des Regisseurs. Das Drehbuch zum Film stammt von Bruno Baratti und María del Carmen Martínez Román und basiert lose auf Shakespeares Tragödie Romeo und Julia. In den Hauptrollen agieren Peter Lee Lawrence, unter dem Pseudonym Arthur Grant, sowie seine spätere Lebensgefährtin, die spanische Schauspielerin Cristina Galbó.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/glut-der-sonne/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:57:14 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>