<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » José Suárez</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » José Suárez</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Reason to Live, a Reason to Die is a 1972 Technicolor Italian spaghetti western movie starring James Coburn, Bud Spencer and Telly Savalas.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-reason-to-live,-a-reason-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Forgotten Pistolero is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Ferdinando Baldi. The film is a western adaptation of the Greek myth of Orestes, subject of three famous drama-plays by Aeschylus, Sophocles and Euripides. Ulrich P. Bruckner puts it among the "most interesting and most touching Spaghetti Westerns of the late sixties".]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-forgotten-pistolero/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Texas, Adios]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Texas, Adios is a 1966 Spaghetti Western film directed by Ferdinando Baldi and starring Franco Nero. It is often referenced in connection with Django, also starring Nero, and although was referred to as Django 2 in some countries, it is not considered a sequel. The film is mostly remembered as a lesser known Spaghetti Western.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/texas,-adios/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>