<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Antonio Casas</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Antonio Casas</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pancho Villa]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Pancho Villa is a 1972 American, British and Spanish spaghetti western film directed by Eugenio Martín. The film features Telly Savalas, Clint Walker, Chuck Connors and Anne Francis. Shot in Spain, this "brawling spectacle" has an often-overlooked light-comedy satirical facet, which to this day often confuses the viewers. The storyline was developed during the Vietnam War and reflected certain antiwar sentiments in an American society.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pancho-villa/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Faccia a faccia]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Face to Face is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film co-written and directed by Sergio Sollima. The film stars Gian Maria Volontè, Tomas Milian and William Berger, and features a musical score by Ennio Morricone. It is the second of Sollima's three Westerns, following The Big Gundown and predating Run, Man, Run, a sequel to the former. Milian stars in a lead role in all three films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/faccia-a-faccia/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Good, the Bad and the Ugly is a 1966 Italian epic Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood, Lee Van Cleef, and Eli Wallach in their respective title roles. Its screenplay was written by Age & Scarpelli, Luciano Vincenzoni and Leone, based on a story by Vincenzoni and Leone. Director of photography Tonino Delli Colli was responsible for the film's sweeping widescreen cinematography, and Ennio Morricone composed the film's score including its main theme. It is an Italian-led production with co-producers in Spain, West Germany and the United States.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-good,-the-bad-and-the-ugly/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Texican]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Texican is a Technicolor 1966 Techniscope film produced and written by John C. Champion and directed by Lesley Selander. It is a paella western remake of their 1948 film Panhandle adapted for the persona of Audie Murphy that featured Broderick Crawford as the heavy. The film was retitled Ringo il Texano in Italy to coincide with the popularity of the Ringo spaghetti western film series.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-texican/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sundance and the Kid]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sundance-and-the-kid/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sundance and the Kid is the American release title of Vivi o, preferibilmente, morti, a 1969 Spaghetti Western comedy directed by Duccio Tessari and starring Giuliano Gemma, Nino Benvenuti, and 
Sydne Rome. The film is also known as Alive or Preferably Dead and Sundance Cassidy and Butch the Kid.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sundance-and-the-kid/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Minnesota Clay]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/minnesota-clay/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Minnesota Clay is a 1964 Italian/French/Spanish international co-production spaghetti western directed by Sergio Corbucci.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/minnesota-clay/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Price of Power]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Price of Power is a 1969 Spaghetti Western directed by Tonino Valerii. The film stars Giuliano Gemma as the hero Bill Willer who tries to get revenge against the killers of his father while at the same time trying to prevent an assassination plot against president James Garfield in 1881.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-price-of-power/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Twenty Thousand Dollars for Seven]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/twenty-thousand-dollars-for-seven/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Twenty Thousand Dollars for Seven is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Alberto Cardone and starring Brett Halsey.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/twenty-thousand-dollars-for-seven/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Return of Ringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-return-of-ringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Return of Ringo is a 1965 Italian spaghetti western film directed by Duccio Tessari and the sequel to the earlier film A Pistol for Ringo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-return-of-ringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Pistol for Ringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-pistol-for-ringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Pistol for Ringo is a 1965 Spaghetti Western, a joint Italian and Spanish production. Originally written and directed by Duccio Tessari, the film's success led to a sequel, The Return of Ringo, later that year.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-pistol-for-ringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>