<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Ignazio Spalla</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Ignazio Spalla</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Mafiamen in the Far West is a 1964 Italian comedy western film directed by Giorgio Simonelli. Its stars Franco Franchi, Ciccio Ingrassia and Fernando Sancho.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-mafiamen-in-the-far-west/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Blood for a Silver Dollar]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/blood-for-a-silver-dollar/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Blood for a Silver Dollar, also known as One Silver Dollar, is a 1965 Italian-French Spaghetti Western film directed by Giorgio Ferroni, written by Giorgio Stegani and Ferroni and starring Giuliano Gemma and Ida Galli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/blood-for-a-silver-dollar/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Pecos Cleans Up]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pecos-cleans-up/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Pecos è qui: prega e muori is a 1967 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Maurizio Lucidi.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/pecos-cleans-up/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[May God Forgive You... But I Won't]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/may-god-forgive-you...-but-i-won't/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[May God Forgive You... But I Won't  is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Vincenzo Musolino.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/may-god-forgive-you...-but-i-won't/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Adiós, Sabata is a 1970 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the second film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini. Yul Brynner takes over the lead role from Lee Van Cleef, who stars in the first and third films.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/adiós,-sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Sabata]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Sabata, is a 1969 Italian Spaghetti Western directed by Gianfranco Parolini. It is the first film in The Sabata Trilogy by Parolini, and stars Lee Van Cleef as the title character. Parolini had previously had a major success with the first Sartana spaghetti western If You Meet Sartana Pray for Your Death (1968), but the sequels were given to other directors, such as Giuliano Carnimeo. Producer Alberto Grimaldi contacted Parolini for a similar series of Sabata.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/sabata/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[I due figli di Ringo]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-due-figli-di-ringo/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Sons of Ringo is a 1966 Italian western-parody film. It was the last film directed by Giorgio Simonelli who, for health reasons, left the production just before the end of filming and was replaced by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/i-due-figli-di-ringo/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Two Sergeants of General Custer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-sergeants-of-general-custer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Two Sergeants of General Custer or I due sergenti del generale Custer is a 1965 Italian western comedy film directed by Giorgio Simonelli.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/two-sergeants-of-general-custer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[White Fang and the Hunter]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/white-fang-and-the-hunter/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Zanna Bianca e il cacciatore solitario is a 1975 Italian adventure film directed by Alfonso Brescia. Despite the title tries to market the commercial success of Lucio Fulci's White Fang, the film's plot has no connection with the novel. The film was poorly received by critics, being defined as "pathetic" and marked as "trash", and gained some cult status in reason of its reputation.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/white-fang-and-the-hunter/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Any Gun Can Play is a 1967 spaghetti western starring Gilbert Roland, Edd Byrnes and George Hilton. The film is directed by Enzo G. Castellari. The film is about a group of cowboys searching for gold, double-leading to double crosses as they continually change allegiances and get the upper hand only to be thwarted by fellow outlaws, mysterious insurance investigators and each other.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/any-gun-can-play/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>