<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>En » Person » Daniel Martín</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>En » Person » Daniel Martín</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:50 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bad Man's River]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Bad Man's River is a 1971 European comedy Spaghetti western directed by Eugenio Martín and starring Lee Van Cleef, James Mason, Gina Lollobrigida and Simón Andreu. Soundtrack was composed by Tony Duhig, Peter Jonfield, Glyn Havard and Waldo de los Ríos.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bad-man's-river/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:48 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Dead Men Ride is a 1971 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Aldo Florio.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/dead-men-ride/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Fall of the Mohicans]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fall-of-the-mohicans/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fall of the Mohicans is a 1965 Spanish-Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Mateo Cano. The film is based on James Fenimore Cooper's novel The Last of the Mohicans.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/fall-of-the-mohicans/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Cipolla Colt]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/cipolla-colt/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Cry, Onion! is a 1975 Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Enzo G. Castellari. It is openly comedic and parodic.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/cipolla-colt/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Duello nel Texas, also known as Gunfight at Red Sands and Gringo, is a 1963 Italian/Spanish international co-production directed by Ricardo Blasco and Mario Caiano, and produced by Albert Band as his first spaghetti western. It was also the first Western to feature a score by Ennio Morricone and the second spaghetti western to star Richard Harrison.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/duello-nel-texas/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Fistful of Dollars is a 1964 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone and starring Clint Eastwood in his first leading role, alongside Gian Maria Volonté, Marianne Koch, Wolfgang Lukschy, Sieghardt Rupp, José Calvo, Antonio Prieto, and Joseph Egger. The film, an international co-production between Italy, West Germany, and Spain, was filmed on a low budget, and Eastwood was paid $15,000 for his role.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-fistful-of-dollars/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[The Return of Clint the Stranger]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-return-of-clint-the-stranger/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Return of Clint the Stranger is a 1972 Italian-Spanish Western film directed by Alfonso Balcázar and starring Klaus Kinski. The film is a sequel to Clint the Stranger.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/the-return-of-clint-the-stranger/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[A Minute to Pray, a Second to Die is a 1968 Italian spaghetti western. It is the fourth and last western directed by Franco Giraldi. It was originally intended as being directed by Sergio Corbucci and the cast was to include also Raffaella Carrà and Renzo Palmer. The American version of the film was heavily cut and handled, including a different ending, and it lasts 16 minutes less than the original version.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/a-minute-to-pray,-a-second-to-die/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2019 02:11:47 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>