<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Dante Maggio</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Dante Maggio</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:32 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Run, Man, Run is an Italian-French Zapata Western film. It is the second film of Sergio Sollima centred on the character of Cuchillo, again played by Tomas Milian, after the two-years earlier successful western The Big Gundown. It is also the final chapter of the political-western trilogy of Sollima, and his last spaghetti western. According to the same Sollima, Run, Man, Run is the most politic, the most revolutionary and even anarchic among his movies.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/run,-man,-run!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Man Called Amen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-called-amen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Man Called Amen is a 1972 Italian Spaghetti Western comedy film directed by Alfio Caltabiano. The film was a box office success and generated an immediate sequel, They Still Call Me Amen.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/man-called-amen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[May God Forgive You... But I Won't]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/may-god-forgive-you...-but-i-won't/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[May God Forgive You... But I Won't  is a 1968 Italian Spaghetti Western film written and directed by Vincenzo Musolino.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/may-god-forgive-you...-but-i-won't/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[For a Few Dollars More is a 1965 spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Leone. It stars Clint Eastwood and Lee Van Cleef as bounty hunters and Gian Maria Volontè as the primary villain. German actor Klaus Kinski plays a supporting role as a secondary villain. The film was an international co-production among Italy, West Germany, and Spain. The film was released in the United States in 1967, and is the second part of what is commonly known as the Dollars Trilogy, following A Fistful of Dollars and preceding The Good, the Bad and the Ugly. The films catapulted Eastwood and Van Cleef into stardom.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/for-a-few-dollars-more/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Bullet in the Flesh]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bullet-in-the-flesh/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Bullet in the Flesh or Il piombo e la carne is a 1964 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Marino Girolami.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/bullet-in-the-flesh/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Holy God, Here Comes the Passatore!]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/holy-god,-here-comes-the-passatore!/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Fuori uno sotto un altro... arriva il passatore is a 1973 Italian adventure-comedy film directed by Giuliano Carnimeo.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/holy-god,-here-comes-the-passatore!/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[My Name Is Shanghai Joe]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-shanghai-joe/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[The Fighting Fist of Shanghai Joe is a 1973 Spaghetti Western kung fu film. The film was released in a number of alternate titles in the United States, including To Kill or to Die and The Dragon Strikes Back. The film was directed by Mario Caiano and stars Chen Lee as Shanghai Joe.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/my-name-is-shanghai-joe/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Black Killer]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/black-killer/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Black Killer is a 1971 Italian Spaghetti Western film directed by Carlo Croccolo and starring Klaus Kinski.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/black-killer/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Shoot the Living and Pray for the Dead]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/shoot-the-living-and-pray-for-the-dead/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Shoot the Living and Pray for the Dead is the original release title of the 1971 Italian dramatic spaghetti western film directed by Giuseppe Vari, and starring Klaus Kinski and Dante Maggio. With its many international releases, the film had additional English titles of Pray to Kill and Return Alive, To Kill a Jackal, and Renegade Gun. The script by Adriano Bolzoni is inspired by American noir-crime films of the 1930s and 1940s, and Kinski's entry into the scene reprises Edward G. Robinson's presence in Key Largo (1948).]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/shoot-the-living-and-pray-for-the-dead/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[100 Fäuste und ein Vaterunser]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/100-fäuste-und-ein-vaterunser/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[100 Fäuste und ein Vaterunser is an Italian-German film directed by Mario Siciliano. It was released in 1972.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/100-fäuste-und-ein-vaterunser/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>