<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel><title>Person » Sergio Martino</title>
    <link>https://www.spaghetti-western.de</link>
    <description>Person » Sergio Martino</description>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:33 </lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Logya</generator>
    <docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mannaja]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mannaja/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mannaja is an Italian 1977 Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Martino. The main role, Blade, is played by Maurizio Merli. Other central roles are played by John Steiner, Sonja Jeannine, Donald O'Brien, Philippe Leroy and Martine Brochard.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/mannaja/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Colt Returns, also known as Arizona Lets Fly and Kill Everybody and If You Gotta Shoot Someone... Bang! Bang!, is a 1970 Italian-Spanish Spaghetti Western film directed by Sergio Martino and starring Anthony Steffen. The feature film debut of Martino after a series of documentary films, it is the sequel of Arizona Colt, with Steffen replacing Giuliano Gemma in the title role and with only Roberto Camardiel reprising his role from the previous film.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/en/arizona-colt-returns/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:30 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Mannaja – Das Beil des Todes]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mannaja-–-das-beil-des-todes/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Mannaja – Das Beil des Todes aus dem Jahr 1977 ist einer der späten Italowestern des Regisseurs Sergio Martino.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/mannaja-–-das-beil-des-todes/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
    <item>
        <title><![CDATA[Der Tod sagt Amen]]></title>
        <link><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-sagt-amen/]]></link>
        <description><![CDATA[Der Tod sagt Amen ist ein Italowestern aus dem Jahr 1970, der in Deutschland seine Premiere am 5. August 1971 hatte. Er stellt eine lockere Fortsetzung des Films Arizona Colt aus dem Jahr 1966 dar. Deutschsprachiger Alternativtitel ist An den Galgen, Hombre.]]></description>
        <guid><![CDATA[https://www.spaghetti-western.de/de/der-tod-sagt-amen/]]></guid>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:51:29 </pubDate>
    </item>
    
</channel></rss>